All right, welcome back to Flagus Talks
the podcast episode 387.
Today on the show, Sarah Hook Sanders
spits in our face with a really tonedeaf
ad. We're going to show it to you. Then
in cringe of the week, we have an
incapable worker section you're not
going to want to miss. It's [music] very
funny. Then after that, I got a ticket
in Southeast Georgia that's going to be
three points on my license unless
[music] one of you can make it go away.
And last but not least, in Urban Decay,
a dad pulls a gun to [music] save his
son from getting beat up, and people
online think he was in the wrong. We're
going to discuss all this and more. It's
Talks the podcast, episode 387,
ranked the best news podcast of all
time. [music and singing]
>> Because words are just words until
action actually starts. And actions
speak louder than words, but at the same
time words speak louder than actions
because sometimes it's the right thing
to do. The right thing to do. Very cool.
Very cool.
>> Sweat stocks podcast featuring Richard
Brown. Richard.
[music]
>> All right. One for one on the intro as
always, guys. Fluoride. The government
has been medicating your water with it
for over 80 years. Not because you asked
for it, not because you voted for it,
because they decided you need it. I
don't want anyone making that [music]
decision for me. That's why every drop
of water in my house is filtered with
Cove Pure. Over 209 million Americans
are on fluoridated water right now.
[music] And here's what the science
actually shows. In September of 2024, a
federal judge ruled that adding fluoride
to water poses, and I'm quoting the
court directly, an unreasonable risk
[music] to neurological health. Not a
fringe study, a federal court ordered
the EPA to act. Then in January 2025,
[music] a study published by JAMAMA
Pediatrics, one of the most respected
medical journals in the world, [music]
confirmed a link between fluoride
exposure and children's IQ scores. The
higher the exposure, the lower the
[music] IQ. Sure, some states are moving
on this. Florida and Utah just banned
fluoride in the water, but that process
[music] takes years, and your family and
friends and children are drinking
fluoridated water right now. [music] You
need something that works now. And
that's exactly what Kofpure is. Its
clear wave reverse osmosis technology is
certified to remove up to 99.9%
of contaminants. Fluoride, PIFAs, lead,
pharmaceuticals, heavy metals, anything
that isn't water [music] gets filtered
out. I love my Cove Pure. It was super
easy to set up. It's basically [music]
plugandplay. The water tastes great and
it looks really sleek and it makes my
kitchen look nice. So, don't wait for
the government to catch up and take the
fluoride out of the water for you. Get a
Cove Pure today. Use my link and you'll
get $250 [music] off. Go to
covepure.com/flecus.
That's c ov.com/fleckus.
$250 off. Thank you to Cove Pier for
sponsoring. Let's get into housekeeping.
All right. Thank you to Cove Pier for
sponsoring. [music] Thank you, Cove
Pure. I love my cove pure. And you want
to know another technique I use with it?
>> Well, I'm going to tell you. I use my
Cove Pure to fill up pots of water for
where I'm boiling water, boiling rice,
boiling pasta, and I use the Cove Pure
water for that. So, it's a full 360 win,
it's called.
>> There you go.
>> Welcome back everybody. Hope you enjoyed
the week off. Uh, thank you to the
members who uh signed up and joined and
enjoyed our content on Tuesday and
Friday, the football highlight tape and
the Richard Rapo show. Very
wellreceived.
>> Yeah, the Richard Rapo show. I we filmed
that before the Lindsay Clancy stuff.
So, there was a point we made about
finding someone guilty and insane that
Utah does, which was a very unique
point. So, go watch it. Rich rap boy
show. Pretty good.
>> And then the football highlight tape.
Check that out.
>> Yeah, sure.
>> That's killing those kids. Got to keep
reliving. All right. I uh just got back
from a vacation. It was a lovely time.
Um I want to tell you guys a little
about it cuz I took some notes.
>> Okay.
>> I took the Hummer on this road trip. It
was 850 miles each way. Hummer did
great.
>> Okay.
>> 8 miles to the gallon. Hummer did what
it could. You mean?
>> But it did great. Hummer was hauling
ass, but it's just not built to go far.
So, I had to constantly keep refilling
it with gas. It runs on gas.
>> Yeah. [laughter] I think the audience
the audience is aware.
>> And then basically you you just start
going and you put it on like 80 mph
cruise control and then the c the fuel
tanks just like
[laughter]
>> you can actually see it move. Yeah. It's
like the minute or the second hand on a
watch. You can [laughter] see the gas
cage go,
>> you know. So, it's basically like I
don't know 100 minutes of driving and
then you fill it up again. So, that was
fun. And then [laughter] I have a
picture here. $130 for 26 gallons of
premium.
>> Wow.
>> 32gallon tank only takes premium.
>> And I saw you said on your Instagram
story, thanks Joe Biden [laughter] for
that one, which is good at this point.
>> It's a good bit.
>> Joe Biden, I did that sticker.
>> But people are messaging me like Trump
too. And it's like
>> obviously it's a joke. We're in a
stupid war with Iran that never
ends.
>> Yeah. But then I saw this funny tweet,
just filled up my car. I'm okay with
Iran having a nuclear weapon. That's how
I felt, too.
>> Yeah, me too.
>> I don't know anything about Iran.
>> Me, too.
>> But here I am at the tank doing 26
gallons of premium, and I feel like an
idiot.
>> I know about the I know about the pump.
I'm at the pump. I might not know about
geopolitical stuff or the straight.
>> Yeah.
>> But uh Yeah. And this I I mean I
actually we had a conversation before
the show because there's a lot of VVC
stuff going on a little less Byron
Donald's stuff but and and gas the Iran
conflict it's you know uh fuel cost and
diesel specifically is an input cost for
everything. So in an inflationary
environment that hurts and it's now
we're a little more than a month away
from the midterms and it's getting old.
But we kind of did discuss tempering our
slander of certain people just to not
hurt the GOP cuz obviously the
alternative for a lot of the GOP
candidates is even worse. But uh I don't
know. So I'm taking my foot off the gas,
my bare foot off the gas on VC where I'm
swaming.
>> So not many miles per gallon on VC.
>> Yeah. Um all right. Like I mentioned in
the intro, I did get pulled over in
Southeast Georgia and it was because a
cop was pulled over on the left pulling
someone over next to the fast lane.
>> Thought you were supposed to pull over
on the right.
>> Mhm.
>> And then I just drove by him and then he
got in the car, ran me down.
>> And he was like, "Oh, you didn't move
over or slow down coming by me." Um, and
then he goes, "What were you going 80
miles an hour?" And the speed and the
speed limit 70. So I said, "I think I
was going 70." Yeah. just kind of lying
to his face respectfully.
>> And he starts writing the ticket
immediately. Yeah. Doesn't
>> And then I hand him my folder with my
license, registration, and proof of
insurance and 20 police badges and
friend of police uh badges and PBA cards
and everything.
>> Everything that's been sent to the PO
box over the last six years or whatever.
>> It's like a binder of like me being a
friend of the police. And he goes, "Oh,
you can keep the police friend stuff. Uh
you should know better." [laughter]
>> Yeah, that works against you. you should
a true friend of the police would change
lanes.
>> That's exactly it. Um and then I said,
"Well, I just want you to know I'm a
friend of the police." And he goes,
"Doesn't matter." So, I knew I was
getting the ticket. Um but basically,
it's three points on my license cuz I
failed to move over. But he was on the
left side and does his dash cam show
that I could have moved over? Was it
clear? Did I not slow down?
>> Your honor, [laughter]
I'd like to inquire on a few of these
questions. You go in a a Sears sucker
suit to a South Georgia court.
>> Yeah.
>> Plead your case. We're going to have to
miss a week uh from now, you know, to
>> So, if one of you guys is a judge, a
cop, a a legal person, a a ticket get
rid of her guy in
>> a fixer. He's looking for a fixer.
>> I'm looking for a fixer in Southeast
Georgia. Please email me at
advertising@fucklealks.com.
advertising fleckistalks.com. I will
respond to that email personally if you
can help me. Um, please. I I need to do
that. Otherwise, I'm just take the three
points and whatever. Okay, we're not
gonna get bogged down in the road trip,
but I went to BIES. Yeah. And I'm not a
BIES fanboy, and I know it's late.
Everyone knows about Bies. Yeah. But I
was really impressed. I stopped in the
Bies in Georgia at 2:00 a.m. And there
were people making fudge.
>> 2 a.m.
>> At 2 a.m. So, like, oh, what's your job?
Oh, I'm a middle of the night fudge
maker at Bies.
>> The overnight fudge manager. Yeah.
>> It was insane. And then I saw this sign
at front out front that they're hiring.
The general manager at BIES makes up to
300K a year.
>> Yeah.
>> The assistant manager, what is that?
175.
>> Yeah. To 250. We've talked about this
before. We've shown this.
>> What is going on? You make 400K
monitoring the Rice Krispies or
whatever.
>> At a certain point, the top tier retail
locations in America like Costco,
Walmart, a Buckies. Like those are the
revenue numbers are insane. So, it's
worth it to pay somebody. Yeah.
>> So, we all got to just go work at
Buckies.
>> No experience required.
>> No experience required. They give you
300K. Hey, you're going to have to work
your way up. And it starts at the 2 a.m.
fudge shift, though. So, that's the
problem, I guess.
>> Midnight fudge bakery. Make 500 grand.
>> Um, and then I was getting updates from
uh the pet place that Jerry stays at,
the boarding facility for the dogs.
>> And then they send me a picture every
day to show me he's doing well. And this
is one of the pictures. [laughter]
>> It's like AI. His legs are twisted or
mangled.
>> So, it's like, all right, good to see
he's doing well.
>> I think
he's okay.
>> He's feral.
>> Yeah. All right. Well, let's get into
the actual show. I wanted to start with
the poll. I realized that we have the
ability to do polls here on YouTube. And
this one was something that you posted
on Twitter and it went very viral and
people were very engaged with it. So, I
wanted to bring it here, too. It's
called How American Are You? Yeah. And
it goes grade A colonial old old stock.
Grade B Antabbellum stock. Grade C Ellis
Islanders. And the dates are kind of
wrong, too. grade D new arrivals 19 I
don't know 75 to present the the ink is
fading on this and then there's like
four subasses after this like migrants
before Joe Biden and then
>> Joe Biden migrant yeah
>> Joe Biden who those aren't even counted
on this list but uh I said I'm a C on
this chart and if it gets to that point
and you guys really need me to I'll
leave
>> cuz I'm I'm mostly uh late 1800s from
both sides
>> very cool and I'm uh early 1900s Ellis
island um grandparents. So, that's very
cool. Let us know in the poll which kind
of American you are. And I think that's
kind of a cool topic. And let us know in
the comments, too. There's some good
stuff to talk about.
>> Okay.
>> All right. Speaking of
>> Yeah, a lot of people want to tell you
if they're old, if they're colonial
stock, and I'll start taking orders,
too. I actually have to defer to you. I
you know,
>> yeah,
>> both of us.
>> I'm down. That's who the real Americans
are.
>> Standing back and standing by
>> for colonial own stock recommendations.
Speaking of polls, uh, some Democrat
poll just came out that kind of shows
how insane the left has gotten when it
comes to Trump and what they want to do
to him.
>> Yeah. And this is just like another
refresher. Sometimes it gets a few
months away from when you saw Charlie
Kirk get assassinated and you kind of
think, oh, they just want healthcare or
something. You get tricked.
>> We can all come together and accept that
that was bad, right?
>> Unfortunately, they're still polling
insane stuff. And so, uh, this the gist
of this is Democrats want Trump out by
almost any means necessary. And the poll
question was, "If you woke up tomorrow
morning and saw the following news
headlines, how would you feel?" And
they're all related to Trump losing
power, facing repercussions, or
potentially dying. President Donald
Trump has been impeached and convicted
by both houses of Congress and has been
removed from office. Of course, that's a
liar dream. 75% support that. Using the
25th Amendment uh uh to the
Constitution, President Donald Trump has
been declared unfit by a majority of his
cabinet. 70% like that or are very
positive about that. Uh, President
Donald Trump died overnight in his
sleep. 45% are very positive about that.
And then that 10% is somewhat positive.
[snorts] Uh, to safeguard the
Constitution, a group of US military
leaders have removed President Donald
Trump from power and assumed control of
the United States. So that's a coup. And
[laughter]
over I think over or about 60%
>> 61% like that
>> or somewhat or very positive. And then
finally, Donald Trump was assassinated
while speaking at a rally. And 23% were
felt very positive about that. 9%
somewhat positive. So,
>> and then 25% neither positive nor
negative, which means you're lightly
positive.
>> You're you're you have a conscience, but
you're you're lightly positive.
>> I know I shouldn't say that, so I'll
just pretend to be neutral.
>> I'm neutral. Yeah. So, they want they're
bloodthirsty. They want him dead. And
then my favorite is the 25th Amendment.
You know, Joe Biden was in office
rambling, doing whatever. The auto pen
was running and nobody even touched
that. Nobody even came close.
>> Yeah. Jim Carrey wore a Joe Biden mask
and pretended to be him and they said,
"Yeah, Joe Biden's 66 now." Yeah, of
course. Uh, but fortunately, when it
comes to the assassination stuff and
like the insinuation of violence, the
types that do respond that way are like
the least physically capable of pulling
it off. It's all like these DSA
>> goldbody retards.
>> Yeah. [snorts] So, it's like not like
something to be fully scared of. And we
actually have a clip here. Um, and then
also besides that, like I'm talking
mostly about the women. The women are
all like unhinged, but the men on the
polls like that, there are a lot of
bisexuals.
>> Yeah. Weak.
>> Weak guys, skinny guys, smaller than
girls, bisexual.
>> Politics is very biological is what I'm
learning more and more. And the low
testosterone guys always fall in line
with the ladies.
>> Exactly. follow they follow the group
because if they don't follow the group
and they stand out that could mean that
they get taken down and they they're
scared like you know how fish
>> call
>> Yeah.
>> they don't want to get whacked
>> and then the fish go into school you
know like that's how they're safe and
then they turn into the picture of the
bigger fish
>> they're prey
>> and then they chase Yeah. like that
book.
>> Um
>> I'm I'm losing you. [laughter] You're
losing me.
>> And then I saw this on Long Island.
There was a election where a DSA
candidate lost and this is how they
reacted after.
>> [laughter]
>> So, she's fainting, whining, and the guy
is, I guess, fighting for wrist control.
[laughter] Stop stop her from
humiliating herself. But
>> you're so close to governing us.
[laughter]
>> No, it's this close.
>> You're so close to governing us.
>> We were going to kill you.
>> Oh, man. That's our plan.
>> That was pretty good. So, you can't be
too scared, but they are kind of
reckless.
>> Yeah. Yeah. All right. they will wield
state power against you. That that's
kind of the key. And that's why I again
with that whole uh getting off the
accelerator on the anti-Byron Vec,
whatever stuff, you guys, all our
opinions are out there. They're on paper
over the last, you know, 50 episodes or
whatever. But again, those type of
people will wield state power to do
whatever they can to you. And they think
it's funny.
>> Exactly. And when they get into state
power and government power, that's when
it gets a little more risky. But on the
individual level, it's just like a
crying Chinese girl who can't manage her
emotions.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> All right, let's get into some homeless
information. I have a little segment
here about a bunch of homeless stuff I
thought was funny, interesting, or
gross. Uh, let's start with this most
Portland scene ever.
>> Yeah, this I at first I thought this was
some sort of modern art piece.
>> I thought this was supposed to be in a
gallery, but
>> I could frame that.
>> Yeah, you could. It says, "Drug
psychosis with a furry onlooker has to
be one of the most Portland situations
I've ever experienced. Within seconds of
starting my walk, I found her writhing
and flailing like she was on flocka next
to the max train line. I called 911. She
was still there an hour later banging
her head against the sharps bin."
>> And then a furry's walking by.
>> Yeah. With luggage. Furry on the way to
the airport. I guess
>> it's pretty nuts. That's what Portland's
looking like these days. Um, and then
this guy made an interesting point
replying to this.
>> If the federal government stopped
subsidizing Nlloxxone, there'd be 25,000
extra deaths a week for about a year.
Then the problem would be mostly solved.
>> That's interesting, too.
>> Yeah,
>> it is kind of how it will work out. It's
not every It's not everybody. Not
everyone needs nolloxxone.
>> Yeah.
>> Just a few people do, and then once they
don't need it anymore, no one needs it.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> I I know. And that's dark, but uh that's
what used to happen, right? And then
like what happened? Oh, he died. What
was he doing? Oh, he overdosed on Fent
and he was uh homeless and he was on the
ground. Oh yeah, that's kind of who
dies.
>> The type of stuff when you get a really
vague obituary and you go, if Max was a
beloved, then he went off the beaten
path a little bit. But yeah, I I I don't
know. We're saving these people so they
can do it again.
>> And it costs money. They all cost money.
We did a stat where it's like a homeless
person in New York is like 80k a year.
>> Yeah, I think it was 83 or 87 if I
remember.
>> Crazy. This next one I thought was
really funny. This is from New York.
>> Yeah. So, Mom Donnie made that big uh
speech about how he was doing public
toilets, and I think there's a a
smallish number of them, like 10 or 11
or something. But it says, "New York
City is rolling out public toilets that
only give you 10 minutes to finish. An
announcer warns if time is running out
before the door slides open, potentially
exposing users to the public."
[laughter]
>> And the reply is, I thought, was the
important part.
>> Yeah. Imagine you in the middle of a
diarrhea dump, but it's a clock
violation. So, the doors fly open with a
buzzer sound. Yeah, it's Looney Tunes
And uh there will be some people
who like it gets
the shack. Remember?
>> Yeah.
>> Thanks for the fack. They wanted to do
that in LA. You think the bathrooms, the
holes aren't going to be used for
fshacks, too?
>> And then like the people
>> I can finish in 10.
>> Yeah. The people it affects the most are
like normal
>> Yeah. Like if it opens on a homeless guy
who's doing drugs, like he'll just move
on. But like what about the people who
are actually going to the bathroom?
>> Totally
>> crazy. Can't have anything.
>> All right, next. Uh LA has a medieval
disease that just out broke.
>> Yeah, Laura, it really is gross because
a lot of times this illness involves
rats and there's a whole bunch of them
across the city.
Oh, rats on the run in LA. And now a new
health warning. LA County investigating
a new fleaorn typhus outbreak in
Wilshire Center. Seven people sick, six
hospitalized.
>> Do anyone has contact with
>> typhus? What's to investigate? They're
investigating. It's like, well, there's
homeless people. They live amongst rats.
The rats carry the fleas. The fleas
carry the disease. Typhus is back, baby.
[laughter] There's no research or
anything. Like, I'm going to go door to
door.
>> But where is it coming from?
>> Where'd it start? Where's patient zero?
Some guy like,
>> how are the rats getting on the homeless
people? They're on the ground.
>> Yeah. So, um, it's interesting because
we always talk about the third
worldification and, uh, import the third
world, become the third world, but I'm
I'm realizing we can also go back in
time,
>> fully eradicated diseases, uh, you know,
1400's era stuff and like plagues. So,
>> feels good.
>> All right, let's move on to our next
piece about California. But before we
do, we have a very special message from
Farmer Bill. [music] Guys, something
came across my desk and I had to let you
know. I was running some Farmer Bills
meat math numbers and I discovered
something quite compelling. Look how
much protein Farmer Bill's meat sticks
have per ounce compared to the
competition. Farmer Bills is at the top
with 14 g of protein per ounce. [music]
Next is Archer Beef Sticks at 8 g per
ounce. Not even close. Followed by Paleo
Valley at 6 g [music] per ounce. Not
even close. as well. Farmer Bill crushes
the competition [music] and he uses
higher quality meat with no
preservatives. For reference, an ounce
of ribeye is only 7 g of protein, while
[music] Farmer Bills is at 14. And it
gets even better when you account for
the cost of protein per gram. Farmer
Bills grades out at the top once again
at 29 cents per gram of protein [music]
when you subscribe and 32 cents when you
do a one-time buy, which is still
cheaper than Archer and Paleo Valley.
[music] The competition is basically
serving you hot dog scraps while Farmer
Bill gives you steak in a bag. Whether
it's the sticks or the bill tongue or
the slabs, [music]
nothing beats Farmer Bills. Load up on
some today. Use code Fleckus 20 at
checkout for 20% off of your order to
save even [music] more. Farmer Bill is a
loyal show watcher and he is on a
mission to create the cleanest, [music]
highest quality meat stacks money can
buy at a more affordable rate than the
corporate competition. Get some today
and tell them Fleckus sent you. Go to
[music] farmer
billillsproprovisions.com.
Use code flecus20 at checkout. That's
linked in the description and the pin
comment. Thank you to Farmer Bill for
supporting the show since we launched
it. And remember, if you guys place an
order, send me a screenshot to my DMs or
to my email and I will follow you back
on whatever social media you want. Thank
you to Farmer Bill for sponsoring. Let's
get [music] back to housekeeping. Farmer
Bill's provisions, the perfect [music]
protein snack.
>> All right. Thank you to Farmer Bill for
sponsoring. Thank you, Farmer Bill.
Those meat math numbers, they add up.
That's good stuff. Um, [snorts] all
right. This next story out of LA is
probably my favorite from Housekeeping.
They will they're trying to pass this
new bill that makes 16year-olds go into
booster seats. Kind of. Yes. Uh,
California want 16-year-olds in booster
seats starting January 1st, 2027. Kids
aged 8 to 16 have to pass a five-step
test before they can ride without a
booster. Fail any step and your
15-year-old, the one who can legally
drive in some states, is back in a
booster seat. Five-part test is uh sit
all the way back, knees bent over the
edge, belt across the chest just so, um
lap belt on the thighs, and number five,
stay like that the whole trip. This is
the state that already treats childhood
like a liability. Now they're writing
height and posture tests into the
vehicle code so a teenager who doesn't
sit correctly can get you a ticket. And
Gavin Newsome signed it.
>> Yeah. And I think they need to do this
to protect everyone from the Modello
illegals who keep crashing and getting
DUIs. And instead of protecting people
by just like arresting and deporting
those people, they want to put your kid
into a teenage humiliation ritual.
>> Yeah. five-point test right before
they're studying for their own license.
Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Um and then let's not forget about the
Indian truck drivers as well. They're
also tearing people up out there.
>> We got to protect them from that.
>> But uh actually you bring up an
interesting point. Mothers Against Drunk
Driving used to be an incredibly
powerful lobby and they were always
doing ads and stuff like that. Where are
they at with the Melo drinkers?
>> They were quiet.
>> Yeah. The Dewey. The Modello. I got two
Dewey. Two Dewies [laughter] Modello.
You know, where are they at? Yeah, that
they got quiet lately. I don't know why.
Good t-shirts, though. You could wear
it, ironically.
>> Yeah, sure.
>> Um, but in California, kids can also do
like hormone transitions, take cross-
sex hormones. They could drive the car
to chop their peckers off,
>> but they need a booster seat. Now, you
got to go in the booster seat, and you
have to wear a little propeller hat, and
you got to carry a lollipop. And it
tastes like poop. And you have to eat
it. [laughter]
>> The lollipop's poop flavored now in
California. I didn't
>> have to eat it. Gavin Newsome signed
that.
Holy
>> And I was thinking like what do a
16-year-old is like what 275 lbs?
>> Yeah. The average [laughter]
the average 16year-old Well, actually I
know you're doing a joke for what you
were at 16. But like the average
16-year-old is like a fat overweight
Hispanic woman now
>> in California. [laughter]
>> So what's the problem?
>> Yeah. I don't know. They're built. Yeah.
>> Um, and then keep in mind that
generation like if you're 16 years old,
that means you were like 10 to whatever
during co
>> so you saw the masks, the compliance,
you got scared, now you're humiliating
yourself in the booster seat. So that
lower than Gen Z generation might be
like the drone class compliance group.
>> Yeah, that's true.
>> They got kind of ingrained at a young
age different than us. You know, we were
our brains are already fully developed
when we had to deal with co
>> Yeah. Yeah. We maxed out our braids,
which we're not saying it went that
high.
>> Our braids are maxed out,
>> but they are maxed.
>> Um, all right. Let's get to this next
story. This is, uh, something that you
sent me that you're kind of passionate
about. Uh, this woman because of woke
sent her kid to a bad school on purpose.
>> Yeah, basically. And since we missed a
week, we're going to kind of go a little
bit backwards to some of the major
stories that we missed just to kind of
cover them. So, some of you guys may
have seen this, but this was written uh
by this woman who, you're right, it was
because of the woke. This woman is kind
of like a solidarity like both racially
and classwise.
And she writes about uh here's her name,
Nicole Hannah Jones. And she says in her
little bio, "I've been reporting on
school segregation and educational in
inequality for more than 20 years, since
my very first job." So, this is kind of
like her lane. and she wrote this very
long piece in the New York Times called
well titled In Fighting for Every Black
Child did I betray my own. A decade ago,
I made a decision about my daughter's
education that I hoped would challenge
New York City's separate and unequal
school system. Now 16, she thinks I made
the wrong choice. And here is the
headline from 10 years ago that she's
following up on which got like praise
and everyone was, you know, ooh, very
deep thinking. I haven't thought about
that. Choosing a school for my daughter
in a segregated city and it's New York
City. How one school became a
battleground over which children benefit
from a separate and unequal system. And
so she's coming at this, this was like a
long my family, my history from grade
zero all the way up 8,300word essay that
this woman was reflecting on. And I
actually like thought I would be more
mad and meaner to her and be like, "You
idiot. Of course you're so
stupid." but it was like honest and like
she tried and she's ideologically the
opposite end of us. But it's interesting
because she cares about her kid but like
had the wrong information and made bad
choices. So I'm going to read kind of a
couple pieces just because there's so
much detail and info out there. So the
the way she kind of starts this article
is she her kid is finally confronting
her after realizing I I go to a shitty
school and I think this was in
elementary or maybe middle school. Um
but my child just shook her head. her
face a mask of disbelief and something
else betrayal. "So you had money to send
me to one of the best schools and you
chose not to," she said, hurling her
words. "Because other kids are
disadvantaged, you didn't want to put me
into a great school." So she's kind of
like peeling back. "What? Mom, I'm with
retards." [laughter]
Uh so Niga was the daughter. Niga was
asking what I'd accomplished by not
choosing the best school for her. And
the honest answer is I don't know. when
it comes to the choices my husband and I
have made about public education these
days. I feel that I failed both my
values and my child. And so that's why
I'm not gonna be mean. It's like this
mom is like trying to learn and
reflecting about this, right?
>> Could have just asked us.
>> You could have paid like a flat
consulting fee. It wouldn't even been
that much.
>> You could have texted me and I'd say,
"Ah, Senator Good School
>> with typo."
>> You could actually you could have asked
any parent. Um [laughter]
yeah. So uh um basically the daughter
kind of realized and eventually she gets
to choose by high school where she goes.
So um she she sent the daughter to a
public school where it's like all the
other mouth breathers, the mo
predominantly black kids whose parents
don't have the money to send him to a
nice school. This woman's like a New
York Times reporter married to her
husband, they have money, right? So it
wasn't a problem. So I'm going to just
read I'm going to bounce around from
anecdotes. Finally, a few days before I
let out for winter break, I received a
folder in Niga's backpack with the math
assignments. This is around middle
school. Uh, I had been requesting since
our conference. Once I tucked her into
bed, I sat at my dining room table and
scanned one page, then another, and
another. None of them were graded. I
started checking Niga's work and
discovered most of her answers were
wrong. Niga believed herself to be good
at math. It was her favorite subject.
But now I understood she thought it was
correctly solving all her problems
because her teacher was not checking her
work. Similarly, Niga's writing
assignments were rife with uncorrected
punctuation, capitalization, and grammar
errors. I sat there silently for several
minutes, conjuring the image of my
little girl, thinking she was soaring in
class when she was failing, and my
devastation morphed into hot rage. Her
favorite subject is math, and she's
getting all the questions wrong. What's
your favorite subject? dieting.
>> Yeah. Yeah. The physics.
>> Yeah. No. And so I I don't want to go
too crazy. You've missed the dieting.
[snorts] But um basically this is like a
sad tale of dysfunctional schools and
and she's going in and out about uh
the lunch is chaotic and the lunchroom.
There's like fights and low limited
supervision and all this stuff. The
teacher's not even assigning homework,
all these things. And she finally finds
out. So, it's interesting that the
daughter like finally finds out she's in
a bad school, she has to be told,
"You're not actually good at math.
You're not doing this right." It's this
weird, honestly kind of messed up thing
to do to your child, right? Um, but long
before Niga started coming home with
familiar complaints, just like at her
elementary school, so she's now in
middle school, her teachers did not
assign homework, and that troubled her
and us. She'd bemoone how the less
experienced teachers struggled to manage
their classrooms and would expend so
much attention on the small number of
kids acting out that they'd be unable to
complete their lessons or help a student
stuck on a problem. There were
occasionally fights in the hallway. So
again, that's like you're stuck at the
bottom 5% is controlling how you learn
in class because they're so unruly and
there's rules against suspensions or
whatever. You're just beholdened to
whatever they think. Right.
>> Yeah. And so then eventually like this
this whole story is kind of framed in
her daughter's awakening where she's
kind of trying to uh exert her will and
choose her own thing. And finally the
mom goes, "All right, you can choose
where you're going to go to high
school." [snorts] Uh I explained our
decision over and over and my but my
answers never satisfy her. But what did
it do? She asked, sending her to the
public schools, like the worst public
schools. Putting me in this school
didn't change anything. I was not trying
to be in this type of environment. It
makes no sense. So, she's arguing with
mom like a teenager argues with mom, but
the teenager actually has more ammo than
you.
>> Teenager's rightwing now.
>> Yeah. Um, it was draining, but I
respected her growing independence and
admired the way she was advocating for
herself. Yet, it also unsettled me. Her
adamance to start uh started to seed a
fear that if I continued to force her to
live my values, it could haunt our
relationship far past her school age
years. That concern led me to a
wrenching decision. I waited until the
next time she brought it up and then I
told her I was going to let her choose
her own high school. Really? Niga seemed
incredulous, even suspicious maybe
peering at me from the corner of her
eyes.
>> She didn't know what incredulous meant
though.
>> Yeah, because of the school.
>> She hadn't gone to a good school.
[laughter] And again, um and so Niga
ends up uh choosing a white school. A
few days later, she handed me her list.
Her top schools were heavily white and
screened their students. the type of
public schools I had spent my career
arguing against, but the link between
race and educational opportunity was
clear to my child. I'd never been in a
school with white kids, and I don't
think I really wanted that, Niga later
admitted. But I thought if you were
looking at the top schools, they're
majority white. So, I kind of was just
like I knew what that's that's what I
had to do, right? So, she ends up
getting into a school um uh one of the
nicer schools. She had to get a tutor
and stuff to get her algebra back up,
the answer she thought she was doing.
Uh, and then here's where the mom's kind
of reckoning with her beliefs. Niga
seemed in her decision to reject my
every belief about public education and
our family's obligation to our
community. But in entering the other
side of public education in New York
City, Niga would soon learn what I had
long known. When it comes to the
education of black children in this
country, there is nearly always going to
be a struggle. It's just a matter of
which one. So then she shifts, you know,
it's all under this this black child
thing. She kind of mentions uh a few
racist comments or casual racism and
it's like but are you learning the
algebra?
>> Yeah. Is it actually racism?
>> So pick your struggle. Failing algebra
the whole point of going to school which
you go eight hours a day or like the
comment of oh your parents aren't on the
upper west side.
>> I like your hair. Cool hair.
>> Mind if I touch it?
>> Racism. Cool hair is racism.
>> So um yeah I honestly we've talked about
this long enough. Basically, the woman
then admits failure. Like she kind of
says like, "I feel like I got cheated."
The daughter says, and
>> there's one quote from this that I want
to kind of everyone to take away where
the mom says, "We had an obligation to
be part of the struggle of our larger
community."
>> You did.
>> And that's what led all this to come
down where the the daughter can't read
as well. She can't do math as well. It
was out of an obligation to be part of
the struggle of our larger community.
That's the black community going to
public schools, right? And so mom and
daughter, well, mostly the mom are like,
"All right, we're gonna grab this
tugof-war rope. Let's go, Niga. Pull."
And then three other kids are fighting
in the corner. Uh, two other kids are
pulling the other way because they don't
know which side to be on. And then
another kid's like beating up a teacher
>> and then shots go off and everyone runs.
>> So yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
Kind of. I mean, it's reasonable, right?
We were talking about middle schoolers
for a portion of this. So, not
necessarily, but this whole like
solidarity and like living by my values
and it kind of goes out the window
when there's just bad kids and bad kids
who are have no uh incentive to learn.
They have no structure at home. And then
this mom is sending her kid where she's
got a loving family with a decent income
sending her to the same stuff and
saying, "Go be bad at algebra and think
you're good."
>> Yeah. But you're part of the the
struggle of the community and it's like,
"Oh, do they appreciate that?" No. Do
they help you? No. Also, no.
>> No. They're fighting over nothing and
they're disruptive and shooting people
and no one can learn because there's a
few bad kids in every class.
>> Yeah. And so, I mean, I just wanted to
cover that because it was it was
fascinating. I give credit to the woman
for kind of coming out and uh coping
with this emotional
uh reveal that you kind of set your
daughter up to fail and she only
scrambled out at the last minute because
you were heavily involved in monitoring.
you got a tutor and you got her out
>> and then made it happen. But uh and
again I I just want to say because we've
covered a lot of this like
administrators growing in schools, test
scores not improving at all. Um
the kind of dollar amount of spending
per pupil that even at schools like this
is incredibly high. There's really no
way to make a parent care about making
sure a kid can read at the grade level.
>> And um
>> I don't know. It's just kind of
everyone's every man for themsself in
America these days.
>> Yeah.
>> And I I know it's tempting to kind of
you want your daughter to have a black
experience or something, but black
experiences aren't that good
>> in America these days. So you you just
get a daughter who you got to get up to
speed on algebra and then eventually she
goes to the white school anyway.
>> Yeah. And then also related to this,
there was a tweet I thought that kind of
summed up the situation very well. You
ask a lib how much they're spending per
kid at the PVP enabled Chromebook
academy in Brooklyn and they say, "I
don't know, $3,000." Then you tell them
it's actually $45,000. And they look at
you like this and say, "Well, maybe it
should be a h 100,000." [laughter]
>> So yeah, I mean that's
>> that's the conversation you have with
like a liberal.
>> Yeah.
>> Who doesn't understand what's going on,
doesn't know the numbers, thinks that
like, oh, teachers need to be paid more.
Oh, we need to spend more on the
students education because we don't
spend enough money. we don't prioritize
our kids and it's like just totally made
up. They have Chromebooks, they get
stolen, they get resold, the the bad
kids are shooting dice in the back of
the classroom. So, um, and the one thing
I'm learning from a lot of these school
things, it's like you are really,
really, really beholden to the bottom
five kids in that class. If they're
disrupting the whole thing, you got to
get your kid out of there. So, exactly.
>> But it was it was very interesting. It's
a woman whose entire like you spent the
last 20 years like arguing about why
it's injust and all that only to get
redpilled by your own experience.
>> Yeah. And then
>> and that's never happened to me.
>> No.
>> Like or you know what I mean? Like a
worldview that I've had has never been
brutally shattered.
>> And she did the article 10 years ago
where she's saying like
>> she probably led people to the
slaughter.
>> That's right. Yeah. Like this is why we
got to do this. This is why it's
important. this is why this is the right
choice and you're kind of doing the
thing where you have the conclusion
before you run the data.
>> Yeah. And you know how a big theme of
our show is I don't want to be part of
an experiment both in America and
whatever and I really don't want my kid
to be part of an experiment.
>> Yeah. And that's what that was.
>> All right, let's jump over to Canada. Um
I wanted to include this. There's
obviously that thing called maid which
is where you can end your own life and
then they encourage people to do it like
oh you have a headache. Oh, you you
broke your leg. You could just end it.
>> Yeah.
>> Um and
>> those are the extreme examples
obviously, but I mean we did cover one
of the maid stories about a guy who got
recruited outside of a Tim Hortons.
>> Remember that?
>> Yeah.
>> So,
>> um so we have the article here. Can you
read that?
>> Yeah. Assisted suicides now make up more
than 1 in 10 deaths in parts of Canada
and rates are rising
>> and 98% of them so far are white people.
Yeah. And like they used to do this back
in the day for the dumb, the lame, the
morons. And these are all medical terms
at the time.
>> Sweden, didn't Sweden basically do that?
Like they uh castrated a lot of their
undesirabs.
>> And now you look now and you know what
Sweden's like.
>> Mhm. And then uh for this they're like
killing the people that actually built
Canada so the migrants can have like
more free stuff faster.
>> Yeah.
>> Kind of dark. And then I found one where
a lady didn't want to do it and they did
her anyway.
>> Our 83-year-old Christian grandmother
was euthanized against her will under
Canada's assisted dying system. She died
covered in blood with her hands clasped
in prayer. So I guess they just kind of
snuck it past grandma. And you know an
83year-old, we've we talked about it I
think last episode about diminished
capacity and the ability to sign away
your rights. And it's like hey quick
when your family's here you want to do
this? They flip a clipboard to you, make
you sign it,
>> make [snorts] you sign it. And then
someone had a tweet replying about this
that I thought was interesting.
>> When assisted suicide has a higher
mortality rate than peak COVID, an event
where you shut down your country to save
the lives of old people, you are now
killing. We live in such a clown world,
it's unreal.
>> It's pretty crazy when you think of it
that way.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And then in Canada, when it comes to
health care, a lot of times the people
will say, "Oh, why can't we have
healthcare like Canada?"
>> Yeah.
>> And I found this story, which is insane.
and this woman has cancer and then the
Canadian health care system made it so
her process to cure it is taking forever
and now she's getting sicker.
>> Women's health in Nova Scotia, Canada is
scary.
I'm so upset right now. I could cry. 2
years ago I get um papsmear. Looks like
you have three cancer cells on your
cervix. So just like abnormal cells.
This isn't anything new for me. Uh my
cervix has been trying to kill me my
entire adult life. I need to send you to
a gynecologist to really dig deeper to
see if it is cancer. Right. The referral
takes months. I get a call 9 months
later from a gynecologist saying, "Hey,
we got your referral. Let's book you and
I'll book the appointment." I show up at
10:00. They're like, "Her appointment
was at 9:00." And I was like, "Excuse
me?" Absolutely not. I am so
diligent with my appointments. 10:00 is
in my scheduleer. She's like, "Don't
know what to tell you." I'm like, "Okay,
so can I reschedule?" And she was like,
"Nope. The doctor said you need a new
referral. You have to start the whole
process over again." I was like, "Oh, I
leave there like crying. Call my GP."
So, she's like, "Let me put out another
referral." That was 7 months ago. Last
week, I get a phone call. Hey, um, we're
just calling from this gynecology
office. You have an appointment on the,
you know, the 16th. I was like, I don't
know about this appointment. No one ever
told me. She's like, oh, no one called
you to tell you that. Nope. I was like,
I can't do it. I'm working on a TV show.
I'm contractually bound. Like, they can
literally take me to court and sue me if
I don't show up. And I'm sorry, but I
don't think the producer cares about my
cervix. So, I was like, I can't. She's
like, okay, well, we'll book you in for
another time then. I'm like, great. When
when is that? She's like, it'll probably
be next year sometime.
>> There you go. You get it. It's dragging
out. It's uh tooth and nail to get an
appointment
>> and you're dealing with like growing
cancer.
>> Yeah. Literally growing in in your body
>> and it's like you're two years away from
even someone looking at it and telling
you what it is.
>> So rich Canadians just come down to the
US, right?
>> Probably. Yeah.
>> They do the medical tourism.
>> Yeah. Medical tourism. Something like
that.
>> And then you know you're you're worried
about your cervical cancer growing in
months and months. And how many uh
foreignb born people are clogging up the
line?
>> Everybody.
>> You got to think like that. If you're
not constantly thinking about migrants,
everything is related to migrants. If
you haven't realized that at this point,
>> and then if you don't like get redpilled
and act on it politically, you'll
eventually get redpilled, but it'll be
when it affects you when it comes to
your door.
>> Oh, yeah. Everyone's got healthcare. Oh,
whoever wants to be Canadian can come
here. Oh, America's an idea. And then it
takes you three years to get like a
cancer screening and then you go, "Wait
a sec. What happened?"
>> You become Hitler. You immediately
[laughter] become Hitler. So, there's
like two ways to go about it. Either you
stop it before it starts or you find out
why the right wing has the views they
have.
>> Yeah.
>> All right, we're getting into our
migrant section, but before we do, I
wanted to show you guys this clip. This
was on social media. It's like these
people getting married and they're
stepping on the cake and then they cut
away to show you like starving African
kids.
>> Don't spoil it, brother.
>> Yes.
>> And they quickly cut and they show you
this.
>> Uhhuh. basically saying like, "Oh, these
people are living so extravagantly and
they're stepping on a cake and meanwhile
this African kid like can't find water.
>> You can't have fun. You can't do bits
cuz there's an African kid in a hut
somewhere starving.
>> You can't have a fun wedding because
Africans can't feed themselves."
>> Uhhuh.
>> You know, and then I have this graph of
the population of Africa. Europe, you
see how Europe is kind of, you know,
>> steady steady slope on that line and
Africa's going parabolic
>> and Africa goes parabolic. And I was
help him too much.
>> Cuz we help him. And I was thinking,
imagine you and me showed up to an
African village.
>> Mhm.
>> First thing would be like, "Oh, so what
do you guys do for water?"
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, every day we walk five miles and we
fill up this oil jug and then we carry
it on our head back and then that's the
water for the day.
>> Yeah.
>> Ah, okay. So, is could we
>> let's get a pump up, [laughter] you
know?
>> Like it's like day one stuff
>> that you have to fix. And then there's
like this idea that like, oh no, like
everyone's impoverished because white
colonizers are stealing all of the
resources. We were gonna process that
uranium and sell it, but the white
people stole it and we that's our
uranium. We were going to use that. I
swear we're going to use that. And then
I found this video of a a person who
I'll just let the video explain itself.
>> Here in the harsh light of day, we
observe a fascinating and highly
efficient foraging behavior unique to
this region. Young males of the local
population have discovered that the
reinforced concrete drainage structures
contain a valuable resource, iron rods.
With nothing more sophisticated than a
broken brick and pure determination,
they systematically dismantle the public
drainage system, extracting the metal
for immediate low value trade. So there
you go. It's the same thing we cover in
LA with stealing the copper wire out of
the active street lights. you know, you
have a drainage system and you go, "Ooh,
that's 20 cents per kilo of, you know,
rods, whatever it is." So, yeah, stomp
your cake, do whatever you want on your
wedding. You You can't teach a people to
function in a society. You can't just
make that happen. And I'm kind of
realizing like, you know, how we have
different forms of government and like,
you know, there are monarchies and
democracies, representative democracies,
and stuff. I think everyone in Africa
should just be under a military
dictatorship
>> or we got to be scared of something.
Yeah, we got to colonize it again.
>> Yeah. Yeah, we just take it.
>> Sure. But yeah, so I don't know. What's
your point here? What's your broader
point? Can't help them.
>> Well, yeah. I mean, I think it's funny
that people say like the people at the
wedding ceremony are the problem.
>> Yeah.
>> No, I think the birth rate and these
people who can't think are the problem.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense to me.
>> Don't get mad at me for having a nice
life. Mhm.
>> Don't tell me I have too many cars.
>> Okay.
>> You know,
>> but that I would even say that.
>> But you see Africa.
>> Yeah. What about them? What does that
have to do with that?
>> I don't know anything.
>> Okay.
>> All right. Let's get fully into our
migrant section. This was from last
week, but I still wanted to show it.
Everyone's still talking about the Texas
Longhorns, uh, Indians, right? And then,
>> yeah, the memes before the Tennessee
Texas game were insane. Texas is
becoming synonymous with Indian slop
now. It's so cool how like college
football and politics are merging.
>> Yes, very much so. Very much so.
>> Um, but then this guy said, "Hope you
enjoyed the game, Bo French."
>> Yeah. His name is Shihan Jaraja
and uh he's an Indian guy and he's on
the field and he blurred out something
on his badge, but his his access badge
says no field and he's on the field.
[laughter]
So, he's scammed
>> and she might have gotten there
illegally, but it's so funny to to walk
into a uh stereotype that you scammed
your way.
>> No, please. Please. It says no field,
but I could get
>> it says field. Did you cover the no? And
then uh the HinduAmerican Foundation
tweeted about the game here.
>> Yeah, that's a Hindu American board
member and a bunch of Texas Longhorns
telling Bo French and his trolls that
we're here, we're not going anywhere,
and yeah, we'll be voting in November.
Yeah,
>> which is, you know, yeah, that's what we
don't want. We don't want you voting.
>> That's true. We know
>> we don't want you here because you form
an ethnic interest group and you start
voting for that ethnic interest group
instead of, you know, for what's right
or wrong.
>> The Medicist had a great reply.
>> Yeah. He said, "Ethnic interest group
reminds you ethnic interest group is
against you forming an ethnic interest
group, but will continue to vote in the
interests of their ethnic group, which
is at odds with your interest." That's
why we've raised the uh raised the
alarm.
>> Yeah. in and with all this H-1B scam and
the Texas takeover of Indians. So yeah,
we know Thank you. We know you're
relying on weight to form a political
group based on your ethnic identity.
That's what we don't like.
>> Yeah. And for many years,
>> so when they fight back, they prove us
right. You know, it's it's interesting.
>> And it's an interesting thing to notice
the change in mindset from their side
cuz for years this was hidden. like
Dallas got taken over by Indians and it
was kind of under the radar for a while
and then people started talking about it
now everyone's talking about it and then
when everyone's talking about it they go
yeah we are taking over
>> so there is a thing where like they kind
of snuck in for a while the numbers got
big enough and now their best interest
is saying yeah we are here we're not
going anywhere what are you going to do
>> and we're a powerful voting block you
know
>> that's where we're at um and then I want
to talk about these H-1B doctors uh
crazy stats came out when it comes to
foreignb born doctors versus American
doctors being hired. Uh we have a chart
here. Can you explain the chart?
>> Yeah, red on the chart is foreign
resident doctors and the gray are
Americans. Uh some hospitals are almost
100% foreign. A lot of these doctors
came in on visas. Some have been tied to
fake credentials and USMLE cheating
scandals because um you know the
standardized tests. There are like
WhatsApp groups going around with the
answer keys and stuff like that. So, you
can't really be sure that someone is
legitimate. Um, I pay the premiums. I
wait months to be seen. Taxpayer funded
Medicare GME money over $21 billion a
year is training these foreign doctors
instead of Americans. And so, these are
some of the worst offending schools.
We're not going to go into it because
this is a pretty detailed chart, but you
can see uh just the insane proportions
here where
>> this is residency program. So this is
like doing that year or two before their
full-time job, right?
>> And the red is foreign born. The gray is
Americans. It's all red.
>> And then these are all just American
institutions obviously. And I don't know
when we got to this point where we need
to train the world's doctors. Like what?
Why do I care?
>> I think it's doc and doctor. It's one of
our best jobs that's like just every
city, every town has it, right? Pretty
much.
>> Yeah. It's one of our best, highest
paying jobs and we're training
foreigners to do it. They're displacing
white Americans who we've already
covered can't get into medical school as
easily. I think do we have it here? That
lawsuit? Yeah. USF uh UCSF med school,
this is from Harit Dylan, is 4.6 times
more likely to admit Hispanic applicants
and 12.6 times more likely to admit
black applicants than white applicants
with the same academic and
socioeconomics background.
>> Yeah.
>> So, we already can't get in. We're
wasting all our spots with foreigners.
And then we've talked about remittances,
language barriers when it comes to
treating a patient, just taking a spot,
whereas an American doctor will spend
all their money here
>> and never return to some other country
because they're only a citizen of
America. So, it's just so
frustrating. Every industry, they hollow
out. They're like weevils or something.
>> And we have
>> they displace the bird. There's probably
a bird metaphor like who tricks the
other bird to raise its eggs and then
they fly out of the nest. It's something
like that.
>> It is something like that. And we have a
couple examples. This is Rockchester,
which is New York.
>> Yeah.
>> And wait till you hear this. 80 are
foreignborn doctors, H1B or J1 visas.
Only two are Americans. So 80 out of 82
are foreignb born. And we have like this
thing here. or we'll just kind of scroll
it in the background of all the foreignb
born doctors,
>> hijabs, foreigners, muhammeds, you know,
>> Chinese
>> Chinese people. Chowo, you pick American
damn you come here. So yeah, I mean it's
like this is a crime.
>> There's a white woman, Paul.
>> Yeah, that's the one. Paulina
Guttermotes. No, they brought her in
from Belgium or something.
Guttermote.
>> No one, man. Crazy. And then uh we have
another example. This is uh from Baptist
Health.
>> Yeah. Alabama Baptist Health. You know,
Baptist.
>> Yep. Uh when you hear Baptist Hospital
in Montgomery, Alabama, is this the
residency class you picture? Broken laws
got us to the point where we have a
doctor trained at the Government Medical
College in Bavagar, India, leading a
residency program where 23 of 24
residents are foreign med school grads.
And so this is the guy Gupta Vicas
Gupta. He's the chair. Here's the
picture of all the uh the residents
there. And 62% of his first year
residents went to a medical school in
his native Pakistan. Seems normal,
right?
>> In Alabama though.
>> Yeah.
>> Maybe there's a maybe there's a Pakistan
to Alabama pipeline that he literally
created. Yeah.
>> Cuz he's hiring all Pakistanis on
purpose.
>> And then uh happened in Texas, too.
>> Yeah. Something changed at the Texas
Health HB/Denton.
Among its current internal resident uh
medicine residents, graduates of
Pakistani medical schools make up uh 25%
of PGY3. I don't know what any of this
is. I'm assuming this is groups of
the residents classes
>> and then 62% of yeah, one of them.
>> So, it's not good. Lots of Pakistani and
they're not better trained over there,
believe it or not.
>> Of course not. And then you get gas lit
once this is brought up. It's like,
well, nobody wants to be a resident in
Alabama. It's like there are kids who
didn't get into a med school and are
like doing software sales now in
America. Nobody wants to.
>> You guys are
>> It could be because DEI lets no white
kids into school and then the American
doctor class is all like those videos we
see on Instagram with all the black
people dancing in the doctor outfits.
The doctor costumes.
>> Yeah, the costumes. I agree.
>> And then they're like, "Well, we don't
really want these doctors. these Indian
people. We'll just bring them.
>> Yeah.
>> And then I don't know, maybe it's
they're cheaper, too.
>> Um,
>> we have a serious problem. The whole
point is like we have such a serious
problem and everyone's just kind of
like, yeah, I saw JD Vance was talking
about H-1Bs. H-1Bs should should be uh
to make America better, not to replace
American workers. And it's like, talk
about the medical school.
>> Yeah.
>> With 80 foreigners out of 82. Like,
they're crimes.
>> And then these residency programs, US
tax dollars pay for them. uh through
CMS, which is the Center for Medicare
and Medicaid Services. So, those are
like billions of dollars in tax dollars
that are paying for these residency
doctors. Let's go over to our next
story. It's about Indians in Texas as
well. Apparently, the ones who are
losing their H-1B jobs are going home
and abandoning their houses. We've kind
of talked about it, but we have a video
example, too.
>> Yeah, cuz they get underwater on their
mortgages and they lose their job and
there's no point. the abandoned ship.
And this guy is, I guess, an inspector
in the DFW suburbs. He says, "Another
day, another inspection of an abandoned
house in the DFW tech hubs. This one was
left unlocked, wide open, and completely
dark. Clean laundry in the baskets.
Personal items everywhere, but nobody's
home. This isn't just a regular market
correction. The decorations inside hint
exactly at who was living here. Likely
another H-1B visa holder who caught a
pink slip. With enforcement tightening
and the immigration clock ticking, tech
workers are facing a brutal reality.
Walk away or get deported. Instead of
fighting it, they are packing a single
suitcase, abandoning their upside down
mortgages, and leaving the keys for the
bank to figure out. The international
flight from suburbia is real. And
remember, we always talk about this
anecdotal evidence first.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, you got to take the anecdotes
first. And uh here's the picture with
the Indian uh elephants. They like
elephants. They do.
>> They won't eat them. They won't eat
them, but they like them.
>> I will give credit. I saw a video of two
Indian guys in India where they should
be, which is nice. Save a baby elephant
from a raging river. Reunited the
elephant with his mother.
>> So, you know, that's great. Don't come
to Texas.
>> No elephants here.
>> Yeah, no elephants here. Get away. Um,
and somebody else said, Fugitive Caesar
said, "A lot of the Indian fraudsters
are fleeing the country and not even
bothering to sell their house because
they're worried about going to prison
and having their assets seized for
welfare fraud." That's the extreme end,
you know, of it. But I'm sure there's a
couple cases like that.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Do you want to play the video?
>> Uh, no. We We saw the pictures. We could
play it quick in the background. This is
what it looks like. They're going
through the house and it's like people
just left
>> the pantry. Yeah.
>> You left in one minute.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah.
>> All the spices. Those are those are up
for grabs.
>> Good sign.
>> Um, and then I wanted to show you guys
this tweet from Insider Wire.
>> Yeah. Breaking home builders say they
can't find workers amid the ice
crackdowns. So they're going to pretend
that like the cost of homes is so high
because we can't find workers and ICS is
deporting people, not because there's a
100 million illegals here and 50 million
legal immigrants here.
>> Yeah.
>> And then we showed you what do you think
happens when everyone the H-1B people
leave Texas? You think those home prices
are going to go up or down?
>> Down.
>> Yeah.
>> And then uh this guy made a really good
point about that tweet though. He said,
uh, why are we supposed to compete with
the entire planet for jobs, but
employers are never expected to compete
for workers? They don't even try to be
competitive in hiring. They simply cry
and lobby for open borders. That's so
true.
>> That's so true. And the homebuilders
should be, you know,
if that H-1B guy who left his house can
see the writing on the wall, the
homebuilders and people like that, they
should appreciate, man, starting in
Obama, you know, 2008
after the economy bottomed out and all
that, we had a pretty sweet ride
building houses with cheap illegal
immigrant labor.
>> It was the golden era. I got rich during
that 12 years, [laughter] you know, like
and now they're whining about uh you
know, but that's a great point about
competing for labor. And
>> there is in in a capitalist system,
everyone says there's no such thing as a
labor shortage. Wages just haven't
matched the demand yet. And so,
it's a theme we talked about a lot. Some
things are going to have to break a
little bit when we're when we're
drastically changing our country from
like this addiction on cheap exploited
foreign non-English-speaking labor.
Yeah, we got a little fat and happy.
We're addicted to drugs basically. We're
going to have to go through withdrawals.
You're in the corner. You're sweating.
You know, we're going to have some
growing pains. Nobody said there
wouldn't, but I mean at the prices homes
are right now, the way boomers are
trading houses back and forth, even
though interest rates are high, it's
like, yeah, I don't I don't know. We
have a surplus of 50 million people
here. Maybe we get that first before we
start complaining about home building.
>> Yeah. As if that's the problem. We can
skip this. Let's go back to California.
This is a crazy stat. It's basically
talks about how undocumented people are
getting tons of uh benefits. Yeah, this
was another big story that dropped when
we were gone from Chris Rufo and I think
the city journal. They basically sent
investigative reporters to California to
figure out the scope of how much welfare
benefits that illegal immigrants are
getting. And the main thesis here in
California, an undocumented migrant
couple with an undocumented grandparent
and two US-born children can collect up
to $100,000 per year in welfare
benefits, all funded by taxpayers. And
so that sentence might be a little
confusing because it says a mig
undocumented couple with an undocumented
grandparent and two US-born children.
That's like the max combo where all the
state things it unlocks to you, right?
So, you have to have US-born kids
because that qualifies you for a certain
thing, but you need to be undocumented
and then if you have a elderly
dependent, then it unlocks some final
shed. Um, the benefits add up. In
California, illegal immigrants can
qualify for CAPI, public health
insurance, and various tax credit. their
children qualify for others, including
Cal Works and as in other states,
section 8 rental subsidies. All told, a
family of five with what what I just
said can get up to 100,000 a year. And
$100,000 a year for someone to pay that
in federal money. This is state money,
but you would have to make 400 grand a
year and then you could support a
migrant family who shouldn't be
here and their stupid kids.
>> So bad.
>> Um $100,000 per year. state leaders are
proud of it that Gavin Newsome bragged
about it on a podcast recently. Um I'm
gonna basically not get into too many
other details, but they call the
headline called it California's shadow
welfare system for illegal immigrants
because they California takes all the
federal money that each state gets and
they administer that. But illegals can't
have that. So they run a parallel state
program. So what what is it in the state
of California? Is it like 10% tax? Do
you remember?
>> Probably.
>> It's close to that. I'm pretty sure it's
like the one of the highest. I I don't
want to speak out of turn.
>> Uh but all that money is going to
illegals. So it's like
>> the federal money goes to All right, we
got to follow the rules on that federal
money,
>> but all the state money we're giving a
brown people who can't speak of
English and we're giving them a lot.
>> Yeah. That's a good dentist.
>> So California man wasting wasting your
>> Yeah. And then we talk about this all
the time, but then boomer Republicans
like Sarah Huckabe Sanders pretend that
the social benefits are being uh taken
advantage of by lazy white people who
just want to hang out in the basement.
This was the ad she released for her
re-election.
>> Yeah. Oh, you want some of this? Take
that. Come on.
>> Meet Brad. Brad has turned relaxing into
a full-time profession.
But you you actually [music] work hard.
You pay taxes to cover welfare for guys
like Brad who just choose not to work.
>> Wow.
>> That's why I launched a welfare to work
requirement.
>> Almost there.
>> Now more Arcanons are [music] working
than ever before.
>> So she's pretending that it's just like
white 20somes who just want to play
video games and not go to work. And then
we've seen this before, too. Um the
speaker of the house did it. What's
whatever his name is? Uh 29. Please read
it.
>> Yeah. It's uh it's not for 29-year-old
males sitting on their couch playing
video games. We're going to find these
guys and send them back to work. That
was Mike Johnson. We covered that on the
show when it came out. Um and Rep.
Scaliz on the One Big Beautiful Bill.
That was when we were doing those SNAP
things. Uh and the federal work
requirements, which we covered, minimum
hours, all that. The 35-year-old who's
sitting in his mom's basement playing
videos games is going to have to go get
a job. These guys are all I don't know
why it's a theme in for Republicans, but
they're all just hallucinating a person.
And if you were going to if you were
going to take an amalgamation of
everyone who got welfare and like you
know how they sometimes face merge every
human on earth and it gives you like
what it looks like, it would be a
severely overweight 42-year-old fat
woman who's who's chocolate brown.
Chocolate brown. More dark, right?
Imagine doing an ad where you had like
Somali scammers or the stats about
illegals getting welfare, legal people,
legal immigrants getting welfare. It
would be a banger ad.
>> Sheniqua brags about flipping her EBT
into cash and selling plates on
Facebook, you know, in the
voice.
>> It would be sick.
>> But then these boomer Republicans need
to pretend for some reason that it's not
what it is.
>> Yeah. Uh the right-wing went crazy on
Twitter over this. She actually came in
and doubled down for some reason. I
don't know why. And also, white men,
especially below a certain age because
the, you know, recipients of federal
money usually are elderly when they're
getting up there.
>> Um, white men are the lowest. It's,
we're the single lowest percent. So,
it's just such an inversion of reality.
And this is the GOP doing it. And no one
has the courage to put a fat,
overweight black woman in an ad and
villainize her, which is so strange
because they're the only demographic who
brags about it on social media. We have
videos of them turning the camera on and
then telling you how they scam you.
>> Yeah. Shane has nine kids.
>> Yeah. Do you want me to read this?
>> Sure.
>> Uh Sarah doesn't understand. So the guy
doesn't exist, but the guy who does
exist is a white guy who's usually been
discriminated against in in lie of, you
know, that fat black lady or someone we
need less white men. So a white guy
isn't doing stuff like this, but they're
usually undermployed.
>> Mhm.
>> Is is the point I'll make. And Nick Plum
said Sarah doesn't understand Brad
wasn't just sitting on the couch. Brad
applied to hundreds of jobs in
Bentonville. He made it through round
after round of interviews and still
didn't get hired. He's sitting on
$40,000 in debt for the education he was
told would give him a future. Meanwhile,
the biggest employer in Bentonville is
laying off and reorganizing corporate
workers while continuing to file
thousands of H-1B labor applications.
That's Walmart. Maybe the story isn't as
simple as young American man is lazy and
refuses to work.
>> Yeah, there you go. And so we're
obviously big proponents of accurate
advertising, right? So we we've often
joked like, what are the ads that white
people can be in? Assisted suicide ads,
the home invasion guy for ADT
commercials,
>> the welfare recipient now, scammer.
>> And so it's obviously a big joke and
it's kind of stupid. But at the
end of the day, Sarah Huckabe Sanders
did make work requirements for welfare
people. So fat black women did have to
get some jobs. [laughter] You know what
I mean?
>> That's true.
>> Like it's it's funny because the
messaging is horrible and they make up a
person and they hallucinate and they
scapegoat a young white guy again.
>> But they did implement the rule to get
the fat scammers off. So I'm not that
mad. It's just a matter of like let's be
honest with each other.
>> Yeah. I wish.
>> Right.
>> Good points. I'm glad we uh settled
that.
>> Yeah. Um, and then I want to talk about
H-1B workers again just because this
stat was crazy and it does play off of
Brad who's too lazy to go work.
>> Yeah, this came out over the break that
we had 76,000ish
tech workers laid off since 2022.
670,000ish
H-1B visas issued to Indian nationals in
the same period. The pipeline never
slowed down even as Americans lost their
jobs by the hundreds of thousands and
were permanently displaced. And here's
the chart.
>> So that's like a one for one basically.
>> Yeah. And that's why I'm saying this
doctor stuff, the H-1B, the tech stuff,
it's a crime. This is all like a crime
has been committed. Something's
happening to you. And Mark uh Mitchell
said this should be torches and
pitchfork stuff. I agree. Hundred
billion dollars in economic benefit
annually wantingly bestowed to the third
world by greedy corporates and their pet
legislators. Legislators.
>> Yeah. Sarah, how could be Sanders? Well,
you know, then I saw this tweet and I
thought it is something to remember.
>> If you think the talent is coming from
countries who haven't even figured out
waste management and proper sanitation
yet, you are a victim of globalist
propaganda.
>> It's easy.
>> I tend to agree.
>> And then the last piece of our migrant
section I thought was kind of funny.
>> Uh, a couple have been mocked online
after they made money renting their
house out to illegal Syrian migrants
only to find out they now can't get
their home back. And uh it says the
title says, "We rented our second home
to refugees. Eight years later, we can't
get it back." And they they get their
picture photographed for this. And uh
somebody else said, "She worked for a
nonprofit helping refugee resettlement."
So
>> I never thought the scorpion would bite
me. [laughter]
That's what you get.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's another shattered
worldview. That's just like the uh the
woman who sent her kid to the all black
shitty school, you know? I've How many
times have you had your worldview
shattered?
I'm asking broadly. Right. We We have
two lib tards and we're not even out of
We're not even into cringe, right? I
can't think of I can't really think of
it. Yeah. Um All right, let's [laughter]
moving on.
>> Okay, let's move on to the final page of
housekeeping. Please tickle and juice.
You know what to do. Help us in [music]
the comments. Make sure you're
subscribed. Hit the like button. Um
>> Rob's in Tuscany.
>> Rob is in Tuscanyany. [music] That's why
I wasn't here last week. I was also
traveling somewhere.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Rob's in Tusky.
>> Flecus is all of a sudden off for a
week. Rob's in Tusky.
>> Robs and Tuskany. Um, okay. I
found out some interesting information.
You ever know anyone who chews ice a
lot? You ever see a guy who's like
constantly chewing ice? It happens when
people are old and sick, especially old
people. They'll kind of chew ice.
Chewing ice means you have an iron
deficiency.
>> Interesting. you're you're yearning for
for iron.
>> So, if you guys if you guys know people
who chew ice all the time or if you have
like old people in your lives who kind
of just get like relief from chewing ice
and you can't explain it, it's because
they're low in iron.
>> Okay.
>> Um, number two,
>> and then you put that little iron fish
in your soup. You ever see that?
>> No.
>> Yeah. There's like a there's like an
iron fish that uh Asian people put in
their pots.
>> Yeah.
>> And the iron leeches out of the iron
fish and then you get more iron in your
soup. They slurp it up in your broth.
They slurp it up, of course.
>> And then Yeah. Yeah. And you can eat the
fish raw, too. You just bite the fish's
head off.
>> All right. All right.
>> Number two. Do you know about pie
plates?
>> No.
>> They're basically plates for pies, but
you can use them for you. And I've been
using pie plates as my plate. And
>> so it keeps them in.
>> It keeps it in. And it's like a bowl,
but also a giant plate. And look at I
mean, it's so much better. And you get
them at the Goodwill store for like a
dollar.
>> You get these cool
>> used poor plates. Used pie plates from
the Goodwill store.
>> The shortest second shortest story ever.
>> Used pie plates for sale [laughter] or
whatever.
>> Um, so I just wanted you guys to know
about pie plates. It's like the best way
to eat.
>> Okay. Actually, while you're while
you're here, I actually have a little
random piece of housekeeping.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'll check if the time's
good. Yeah, you can do it.
>> Plastic plastic razors. Have you guys
ever heard of plastic razors? I'll grab
I'll grab a picture.
>> Not for like your face, right?
>> No, for like scraping
>> Yeah. Yeah. Scraping.
>> But for scraping you don't want to
damage.
>> So, I bought this on Amazon. It was like
$9 and it came with a bunch of
replacements pl like a straight little
razor blade thing. And then if you have
like gunk or you know there's something
on your car or surfaces that you want to
use your car.
>> I don't know. I
>> cuz I had a decal fall off my car and
then it left like the residue of the
glue.
>> You scrape it off
>> and I can spray it with some stuff and I
can hit with the thing.
>> So plastic razors, it's kind of a
misnomer.
>> Rob the car guy, let me know if I can
use plastic razors on my car, please.
>> I wouldn't recommend on people's paint,
but tables, the gunk, like anything you
you got gunk buildup anywhere. I used
it. I'm sold. I'm in. So high plates and
plastic razors. Yeah, that's the
takeaway from today's episode. Um, and
then this is something you sent I
thought was pretty funny.
>> Yeah, we're still in my part of the
final page of housekeeping. There's a
story that we're basically skipping that
happened while we were gone. Um, here's
the title from the article. Saturday
night at the Massachusetts lesbian bar
everyone is talking about. And there's
this bar called Last Ditch, a bar and
art space, ended its COVID mask
requirement as a way to attract more
people. What it got instead was outsized
detention. So woke lesbian bar that had
a mask mandate all the way up until
September 26.
Finally said, "All right, guys. We're
calling it time of death. September 26,
6 years after CO started or whatever it
is." Um,
>> also the name last ditch. I'm trying to
figure out how that's like a disgusting
sexual pun, but I couldn't figure it
out.
>> Rotten clams. [laughter] All right.
Sorry. Sorry. Um, so basically we're
skipping that story. You can use your
imagination on who the management was,
who who protested against it, all that.
But, uh, people were, it was kind of did
a conversation about these lesbian bars.
And it's a call back to something that
we covered. I think we made it the
thumbnail of an episode. It was about
Gen Z faking disabilities. Basically,
the younger people, they fake canes,
they fake having POTS, they go to
constant doctors until a doctor finally
says, "I guess it's POTS. just leave me
alone. Right?
And it matched with another thing we
figured out a long time ago that gay
guys when they wake up from surgery,
they go, "Where am I?" instead of,
"Where am I, bitch?" So there's they
wake up from anesthesia and there's no
gay voice. A similar thing is happening
with the Gen Z people who fake their
disabilities. And this is from a random
commenter with no credibility, random,
but it rings true and it's anecdotal.
and they said, "I work at a different
lesbian bar in the country, and can I
tell you the amount of canes that get
left behind at the bar because they
forgot about them the second they
actually get drunk?"
>> Ah, so the people who with fake the
disabilities and yes, this is my cane,
my mobility aid, they go start drinking
a little, who [laughter]
leave the cane at the lesbian bar.
>> Wow, that's funny stuff.
>> So, it's not really worthy of its own
section, but I wanted to get that out
there. Final page of housekeeping.
>> All right, final page of housekeeping. I
have a bunch of fun sports stuff. Uh
we're going to go quick u because we're
running out of time. U but I just want
to show you guys fun sports stuff. The
head coach after a big win does some
blood ritual.
>> He wipes the blood, wipes it on his
face. Blood play.
>> Blood, sweat, and tears.
>> That's cool though. I like that. That's
Americana.
>> Yeah, sure.
>> Next. This is an interception. And then
the guy who tried to catch the ball on
offense tackles someone like crazy. This
guy's a highly recruited tight end,
right?
>> Yeah.
>> So, he throws the ball, gets picked.
[screaming and cheering]
>> Is that illegal?
>> I don't think so. They throw the flag,
but it's like this shouldn't be.
>> That's a clean slam, dude.
>> That was a clean slam.
>> So, that kid's going places.
>> Okay.
>> Uh, then next, I saw this. I thought
this was interesting.
>> Uh, yeah. This is from the Missouri game
and it says it's uh apparently there's a
problem with the running back depth on
the Tigers.
>> They're the Tigers, right?
>> And uh Malay Fouti, he has a torn ACL.
And Ahmad Hardy, he has a gunshot wound.
He's still recovering from a gunshot
wound.
>> Yep. Uh so this is all fun sports stuff.
Okay.
>> Uh this was after a big win and then the
security tries to stop people from
storming the field, but he can't.
So,
>> he's doing his pass sets, but he's just
kind of like hitting him. He That's a
girl.
>> Got a girl. The only one he got was a
girl, and it actually worked.
>> The battle is lost and he hits a girl
with a forearm shiver and cute dress.
She just wanted to have a nice night.
She saw other people. She wasn't leading
it.
>> She's taking a picture.
>> Poor girl.
>> And like after a certain point, it's
like no one no one's stopping anyone.
You can't win.
>> It's over. All right. I stopped this
group. Everyone else is on. Uh next, uh
there is a new commit to the 11
Warriors. Can you
>> Ohio State the Ohio State basketball
team has
>> Yeah. Can you uh read his name?
>> Dang Nagore.
>> Yeah, there you go.
>> Dang Nagore. So, congratulations to him.
>> Fun sports stuff.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And then uh this was a botched home run
catch attempt by a fan, an old fan.
>> Old man. He brought the mitt. Boom.
>> Missed. He had the glove, too. And he
got it right in the face.
>> The hat took some of the thing off.
>> I don't know. Depth perception when
you're old.
>> Eyes on, man.
>> Here it is. He's got his eyes on it the
whole time.
>> Right in the face.
>> Poor guy.
>> Tough. He's okay.
>> Okay.
>> Um,
>> did you make that up?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. You
>> the other So, this is all fun sports
stuff. The other day, uh, a couple days
ago in Tropicana Field in St. Pete,
Tampa, where the Tampa Bay Rays play,
there was a game between the Red Sox and
the Cubs because there was a storm and
they had to play a game.
>> Uhhuh. And then I was telling Rap Boy
like that's almost like a a dream like
oh I had a dream we're in Tropicana
Field but the the Cubs were playing the
Red Sox like you would never ever see
that in real life
>> and then it kind of happened.
>> Okay.
>> So I thought that was interesting. Okay
so we showed all the fun sport clips but
you know what that means when we show a
bunch of fun sport clips we also have to
show gay sport clips
>> to balance it out.
>> To balance it out. So this is the first
one I found.
>> Says come do my makeup with me before my
baseball game. Come with me as I do my
makeup before my game in front of
thousands of people as a professional
baseball player.
[laughter]
>> I always like to start with pink eye
black. I'll switch out my designs
before.
>> All right, that's enough.
>> Yeah. What is this? Savannah bananas
>> I was going to say, is this a Savannah
banana?
>> I think it's the it's the people who
come and get killed by the Savannah
Bananas. [laughter] I don't know. I
don't know how that league works.
>> Yeah. I mean,
>> bunch of twink you know.
>> And then uh another gay sport clip.
Unfortunately, can you read this guy's
name?
>> Yeah. What? He's He's playing. He's on
Liberty. That's our school. That's like
a We like Liberty.
>> Yeah, I like Liberty.
>> But his name is a DB number seven. I
blew a guy.
>> I blew a guy.
>> I blew a guy. 62 200. He looks good.
He's a fifth year from Ocala.
>> He's an otter.
>> All right.
>> He's a muscle otter.
>> Okay, chill.
>> And then, well, we probably like him. I
blew a guy. We'll send you a shirt. Um,
and then there's
>> a liberty, you know. Then I found this
guy who works for the Yankees I believe
and he just does his outfits like while
he's doing the Yankees events and he
works in like the Yankees I don't know
front office I guess and this is what he
wears.
>> Sports fem guy live from Sports
Illustrated Stadium. I'm here with my
boy Gino. Gino, you like gay people?
>> Of course. Of course.
>> I'm here with my ally Gino. Tops H&M
skirts. Princess Polly shoes. Steve
Madden earrings Ali Weiss jewelry.
always. Let's go New York City FC.
>> You see he's wearing the the shoes with
the nail polish.
>> Testosterone level is 89. A doctor is
warning me about this. And we have
another clip from Yankee Stadium.
>> Sports Fing guy back at the best stadium
in the world, Yankee Stadium, the
Cathedral. The fit is insane today. One
of my favorite outfits ever. Dressed
from Mango shoes full on. They are
absolutely killing my feet. Cannot wait
to take these off the second I get out
of here. But the fence laid today. Worth
the pain.
>> What does he say at the beginning?
Sports can be gay.
>> Yeah.
>> It's like, brother, not here.
>> Yeah. I I guess you can and if you don't
get fired and now they have to be gay.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> But that guy looks like someone you'd go
to high school with.
>> Yeah. Yeah. He got hijacked.
>> I was thinking like, oh yeah, he grew up
next to a golf course under some power
lines.
>> Yeah. And like some toxic sludge got
buried there 40 years ago and his
asbestous is still in his roof. Like
it's a six things happened at once.
>> He's eating got some chips.
>> Mom, I want to put on a dress
>> but something.
>> What are you talking about Anthony? You
want to put on a dress?
>> But something happened like he looks
like he looks like a normal guy who lost
like a fantasy football bet.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> I don't understand what happened.
>> Sometimes Sometimes we show you a clip
and there's nothing to learn. There's
nothing to learn. There's just some
hypotheses that'll come up.
>> I didn't know they made them like that.
>> Yeah, I didn't either.
>> Um, all right. Well, that is the end of
housekeeping. We're now moving on to
cringe of the week.
>> All right, our first story from cringe
of the week. We basically have an
incapable worker section here
>> and we're going to start with our own
government. Uh, here we have Jim
Justice, I believe is his name, and he
had a dog birthday party parade.
Happy birthday
to you.
Happy birthday,
dear baby dog.
Happy.
>> We're also $40 trillion in debt. We have
100 million illegals here and we can't
pass the Save Act.
>> There's a hospital with 80 out of 82
foreignb born Indian type doctors. So,
>> dog dog had a cute birthday. dog
birthday. Take your dog birthday.
>> Yeah.
>> Bad.
>> All right.
>> Next. Apple has an online kickboxing
class that you can like click and follow
along at home. And the person who's
doing it is this woman.
>> Asalam alaikum, champ. Coach Nez here
with a 20-minute kickboxing workout for
you.
>> It's a Muslim woman doing sign language
teaching a kickboxing class.
>> Yeah. In a Nike hijab. So, it's like the
corpses. Apple is still so successful
they can waste your time a little bit on
this but they're like laughing at
Nike while doing it. It all bad.
>> Yeah.
>> And you guys probably saw this from last
week. Uh Mets player got like seriously
injured. There was a collision where
someone kne him in the head and it just
like knocked him out out and then he had
to get saved on the field. We'll play it
in the background here. And then this
fat guy saves him. And then this woman
who can't lift up the thing
and he
>> they can't lock it out
>> and he has a neck injury and the guy's
banging his head into this guy's gut and
then they come to load him onto the golf
cart
and they're really banging him around
for someone with a neck injury.
So you're a multi-million dollar
contracted MLB player on the field. you
get a horrific injury and some obese man
who who doesn't even look strong and a
woman
>> who's 4 foot 11
>> who's who's you know not not good either
they come and they jar your neck around
right on the way out
>> and like any
>> and who's the driver an Indian guy is
the driver [laughter]
>> and then any of the Mets players
standing in the background could have
been like more capable to help.
>> Yeah, they just show me where the lever
is. Okay, got it. Smooth transition.
Yeah.
>> All right, next.
>> I'm tired of seeing sloppy fat. I I I've
there was a famous clip in a soccer game
where a guy was horrifically injured and
some medic runs out and he's a fat
idiot. He's from the other side of the
field and one of the soccer players runs
to him, grabs his medical bag that's
weighing him down, sprints and fries it
over to the injured player. So like this
is like a long time thing.
>> Crazy.
>> I don't know. I I guess Oh, I can't
discriminate against you because I don't
know there there's no rules about being
able-bodied to do a job where you're
obviously going to need to be able.
>> All right. Who's going to be the
fireman?
>> Uh, Deb.
>> Fat Deb. The lesbian bulldike. Take your
mask off.
>> And then next, um, we'll just play this
in the background. It doesn't require
sound, but there was, uh, President
Xiinping and President Trump had a
meeting and then the Chinese whatever
came and then there was an issue where
Secret Service got mad at this Chinese
reporter. But we still have Secret
Service women. That's the takeaway. And
I was thinking, are these women the most
capable and qualified people we have?
Like these two are the best and we can't
get better and that's why they have the
job. And if the answer is not yes, we
should find a man who can actually do
it.
>> Yeah. And the answer obviously is not an
enthusiastic yes.
>> Yeah. And then we have a firefighter
here um who is struggling to control the
hose
>> during an active car fire.
That's two. That's twice. Spray your
buddies.
>> And like this is a guy and what maybe
it's training
>> proby.
>> It looks like maybe he's not holding it
at the right angle or whatever. And
there is a thing where like firemen will
line up in support and say like relieve
the nozzle man. Like relief relieve the
nozzle man.
>> But come on.
>> Yeah. What happened? Not very good. Um,
and then we have a story here of a
fireman who is good, but they wanted to
make him not allowed to be a fireman
anymore. And check out why
>> career out of it would be uh the goal to
get paid to do what you love.
>> But Andrew's application to the Fremont
Fire Department has been rejected by the
city because his high school diploma
shows he's been homeschooled, which is
an unacredited education in Nebraska.
Yeah,
>> we're not mad about one applicant, my
application. I think now it's turned
into we want to make sure that every
homeschooler has um an equal
opportunity.
>> So, that's the key. And there is
something deeper here where they want
like homeschooling to be illegal. There
was a tweet that kind of sums it up, but
this is like the start of it.
>> Yeah. This, by the way, is how the left
will ban homeschooling. They won't draft
a piece of legislation that says
homeschooling is illegal. They will just
create a world where you can't get a job
or go to college if you are
homeschooled. They will force parents
hands. And this guy is already a
volunteer firefighter. He wants to move
to paid. And I guarantee if there was
still an aptitude test for the fire
department, he'd be like at the top.
>> Yeah. So
>> he looks physically capable. He likes
the job.
>> But they needed to go to migrants, I
guess.
>> Yeah. So any broad themes for your uh
competent incompetent workers section?
>> Lots of incompetent. No more
homeschools. The goal.
>> Yeah.
>> Something like that.
>> Okay.
>> All right. Next, we have a person who is
uh too fat to be bathed at the hospital
and they're mad about it.
>> I'm so tired, y'all.
I've been on the phone all morning and
tired. I guess I'm just getting
discharged right back to the facility.
Girl, I called DCF this morning
to try to see if an investigator can
come and try and block the discharge.
the hospital. They're ready to send me
back out today, girl. And most likely,
I'm gonna be discharged back out today.
I sure am. It's like they don't care
that I don't have a a a bed that doesn't
work. I don't have a chair that I can
get into. They don't have people that
don't want to come bathe me
properly because of my size. The
fact that I can't there's no
microwave there at the facility.
the fact that I wrote a
grievance on the fact that the CNAs
can't get like if I buy food meal I
literally buy food to get heated up
healthy meal prep food they can't take
it to the kitchen cuz we don't have a
microwave. They have to take the food to
the kitchen. The kitchen has to properly
heat the food up. There's barely any
kitchen staff to begin with. And
then the kitchen staff get mad at me
because they feel like I'm I'm writing a
grievance on them personally. No, I
never wrote a grievance on the kitchen
personally. I would agree with
>> So he doesn't like how the people
>> I think this is a woman and that
dubtales into the point about once you
get so fat you lose your gender.
>> You just have various shapes and you
kind of merge into one thing. I think
this is a woman based on the no beard
cuz a fat guy wouldn't maintain his
beard. Someone who's in the hospital
like this.
>> That's a great point. So, I I was going
with woman.
>> So, pardon me. Uh, she doesn't like how
she's not being or how they're bathing
her.
>> Yes.
>> Do you have a problem with how people
bathe you? How do you deal with this?
>> I don't know. I've never had it happen.
I've never been in a hospital like that.
>> So, I I'll have to defer. I'll I'll tell
you when I when I get bathed.
>> Um, I I have a couple points to make.
Remember we showed a fat girl a long
time ago and how how you're like stuck
in there? that theory like once you're
so fat you're stuck in there. You're
like help I can't hear you, you know.
>> Yeah.
>> Um so she's stuck in there. But I don't
know my main theme is and we just
covered all the Indian doctors and stuff
and I'm not bathing you. You're 490
pounds. I can't bathe you. Whatever. But
you see how a certain type of person has
problems everywhere and it's like you're
dysfunctional. You're up. You
can't control your weight. You're in the
hospital because of weight related
I'm assuming. And then you got a problem
with the people who bathe you, with the
nurse, with the some sort of billing
officer, the kitchen, the bed, the
chair. None of it's up to standards,
right?
>> I I don't know this. It's just like a
miserable type of person where you
could get any situation and there'd be
like a list of complaints and not one of
those complaints would be, "Man, I wish
I wasn't 600 lb."
>> Yeah. The world's not built for people
who are 600 pounds.
>> How's the world going to change instead
of me right now?
>> Yeah.
>> So, I don't know. I I just threw this in
because it pissed me off. And that's one
of those
you know how we get the all the EBT
scams, we get the uh you know the
federal Medicaid scams, we get all these
type of money scams, but the one thing
we can't look into because of HIPPA is
the hospital. And I'm afraid that all of
the hospital expenses are illegals and
then people like this who like want to
live at the hospital.
>> So true.
>> So I don't know. I just when people film
it themselves, we have to kind of show
you.
>> Yeah. Cuz it's hard to get in there.
>> Yeah. It's hard. The doctor's jobs
depend on it, right? And then as we
know, half the doctors are
foreigners, so they're not even
communicating with with us on the level.
So I just wanted to get that out there.
All right, let's get to our next story.
Uh, Miss Rachel has an interesting
theory about how the rightwing isn't
actually Christian,
>> the rights of children here, SNAP
benefits being taken away. That was so
psychotic. And Rachel, it's like is is
>> in the name of Christianity, too. Let's
be a more Christian nation and take away
SNAP benefits.
>> Who said that?
>> Let's be a more Christian nation and put
our neighbors and the stranger, which is
in the Bible as like
>> welcome the stranger. put the strangers
in detention centers,
>> right?
>> And like it's just
>> it's so psychotic. It's it's
>> and let's make more and more money and
not help others and and let's deny
people's healthcare. It's like but the
SNAP thing, I mean, that just breaks me.
you're going to complain about a child
having enough food and like I'm so
excited that I heard from Troy um who's
running for Senate in Maine
>> um that they have free lunch at the
schools and I'm like that's awesome.
>> Oh wow. And it's like she's t she's
trying to classify SNAP as charity.
>> Yeah. [laughter] That's our tax dollars.
It's going to Doritos and fat inner city
moms with eight kids. I don't know what
what everyone thinks.
>> As if it Yeah. as if it's like, "Oh,
this is the orphan food bank. We're
shutting it down because of Trump."
>> It's like charity isn't giving people
free money to do whatever they want
with.
>> And that was just kind of interesting.
There's a tweet that sums it up as well.
>> Yeah. One of the most replicable
findings in all of American political
statistical analysis is that Republicans
give significantly more to charity and
volunteer more for the poor than
Democrats do. It's not even close. It
never has been before. or it never has
been close. And that was something uh
we've covered on the show that Democrats
like to vote their charity in and a lot
of Republicans actually like to do the
charity. And then there was another
study that references this that as uh
the homogeneity of a population
decreases then charity and helpfulness
does too. So multiculturalism actually
gets in the way of people volunteering
and contributing time and money
>> because you don't want to help by just
giving your money to Indian people.
foreigners who got here yesterday. Yeah.
No thanks.
>> People who don't appreciate it.
>> This Rachel is on a absolute terror.
Nolan Wells didn't drown. Black people
don't hang themselves from trees. The
right isn't Christian because they took
away that program that was getting
massacred. She's a real certain
type.
>> She got the $50 million deal.
>> She and she references the Bible so
easily. I think she's a Unitarian.
>> So she's does whoever comes up
and talks at the podium, she goes like
this. [laughter]
All right. Well, that's the end of
Cringe. We're now moving on to Urban
Decay.
All right. Our first story from Urban
Decay. A doctor was murdered for no
reason. Detectives say that he broke
into the home. This couple was sleeping
and they say that he started attacking
them, stabbing them both multiple times.
Uh, and the couple, they say, fought
back. The motive is unknown. Now, police
say Hemingway entered the home on Lynen
Avenue in Edgewood through an open rear
window. KDKA captured the moment
Hemingway was on a stretcher and wheeled
into an ambulance. Police are not sure
if he knew the couple. According to the
criminal complaint, the victim's wife
told police she and her husband were
sleeping and they woke up. She described
the man as quote psychotic and said that
he repeatedly made utterance about God
and being God. The suspect was in his
underwear during this attack. She
recalled her husband calling the suspect
Elijah. The mom was able to yell for her
two kids to get out of the house. They
did and were not hurt. County police say
a Monrovo Police Department K9 unit
tracked the suspect down to Evans's next
door neighbor's home. They found car
keys where they found him. Hemingway had
cuts to his hands. The victim has been
identified as 46-year-old Dr. Idris
Evans. He was the medical director of
the pediatric critical care transport
team at UPMC Children's Hospital.
>> Very sad. And the doctor was the white
guy.
>> Ah. Ah. Yeah. Yeah. And he was like a
beloved guy in the community apparently.
Someone kind of talked about that uh in
a long write up.
>> Yeah. The brutal slang from yesterday is
actually getting attention as the victim
was a highly regarded pediatric doctor.
But the details of the savage scene that
unfolded near Pittsburgh, PA, and the
ongoing insanity of our justice system
must be fully articulated. In the
overnight hours between Wednesday night
and Tuesday morning, um, that doesn't
sound right. A black criminal already
out on Z bail for firstdegree felony
burglary and thirdderee felony theft
broke into the home of a white
46-year-old doctor named Idris Evans and
his family. The soon-to-be killer, black
32-year-old Elijah Hemingway, ascended
to the third floor of the home and
entered the bedroom of Idris and his
wife, Gina. As the couple slept, kitchen
knife in hand, wearing nothing but his
underwear, Hemingway attacked Idris and
Gina while screaming about himself being
God. Upon the couple's rapid awakening,
a brutal struggle unfolded in the
bedroom. The scene was described as
extremely violent with broken furniture,
smashed mirrors, and blood covering the
wall uh and floors. As Hemingway
repeatedly plunged the knife into Idris
and Gina Evans, Gina screamed aloud to
awaken their eight and 12-year-old
children, bellowing for them to flee the
house. The children did and escaped
unharmed. Gina eventually managed to
escape as well, surviving multiple
severe stab wounds and lacerations.
Idris, however, bled out and died as his
own in his own bedroom where minutes
before he had been peacefully asleep
with his wife hours from awakening for
another day of duty at Children's
Hospital of Pittsburgh.
>> So, we get it. That's brutal. But in the
middle of the night, you wake up and
someone's just stabbing you and killing
you and then you're thinking, "Oh, I'm
just going to die, but at least I'll
yell to my kids to get out of the
house."
>> Well, and that's kind of the duty once
someone's already in the house is you
have to fight the attacker long enough
for everyone to escape. And
unfortunately, if you don't have a gun
next to your bed and you don't close the
windows in your house, I mean, that's
I'm looking for lessons. Usually, the
open window. It sounds like Elijah knew
this guy or he called him Elijah. So,
there might have been some history, but
we don't talk in uh these these uh body
cam mental breaks where I'm God and no
man can stop me. There's a lot of the
same like bravado and energy. They have
a similar mental break.
>> Yeah. And then someone had a dumb theory
about this.
>> A lot of social justice warriors on
Facebook, especially leftist white
women, are trying to insinuate the black
man knew this white doctor and maybe his
son was like a patient of his. There's
like no basis for this, but that's what
they're trying to do. Maybe there's an
explanation for why he would do this.
>> Yeah. [laughter] Yeah.
>> It's like they're doing the Lindsy
Clansancy thing.
>> Well, the guy knew his name, so that's
what they said. So,
>> yeah. So, not many people are going to
be talking about this story and it's
>> Well, it'll die after 24 hours.
>> Exactly. It just becomes like one
headline, a 30 secondond piece of the
local news. But don't worry, they're
doing the stop the lynchings panel
conversation. That That was last week.
>> Yeah. This is from September 18th. All
these black and brown faces are talking
about stopping the lynching. And
remember, not a single white person has
been involved. There's multiple black
people arrested and then multiple
confirmed suicides so far from the
hangings. So,
>> and this white guy got lynched.
>> He got stabbed to death.
>> That's a lynching.
>> Yeah, it's a it's a violent violent
murder. So,
>> depending how you Yeah, exactly. And
then uh our next story, we have two hit
and run stories that are really crazy.
The first one's from Chicago.
>> Yeah, this is kind of I'd call it a
South African story. South
Africanization of America because
>> everybody you encounter at the lowest
moment is not helping you. So a Chicago
Police Department dispatcher was trapped
in her wrecked car with nine broken ribs
and two fractured vertebrae desperately
waiting for help to arrive. That's when
this couple alle allegedly slid into her
car, stole her credit cards, and patted
her down for valuables.
>> So she was like incapacitated, like
unconscious and up after
>> I'm trapped. Get the seatelt off.
>> Yeah. Waiting for first responders to
come and someone comes in and steals
everything you have.
>> Yeah. And not only that, um, but this is
I'm going to read from the story. A
veteran Chicago police dispatcher was
pinned inside her wrecked car with nine
broken ribs and two fractured vertebrae
when a man climbed into the back seat
and stole her driver's license and
credit cards. Prosecutors say the man's
girlfriend then got into the front seat
and began patting the injured victim's
waistline, apparently looking for more
valuables. Uh Victoria Messerina, a
dispatcher with the city's emergency
management and communications for 26
years, was driving home in uniform when
another vehicle slammed into the
driver's side of her car at the 3,300
block of West Douglas Boulevard around
2:30 p.m. July 3rd. The other driver ran
away, leaving Messina trapped in the
damaged vehicle. A bystander let her use
his phone to call 911, but the wreckage
in her injuries kept her from getting
out. So, it's a hit and run already. And
then you're trapped in the car waiting
for help. And who comes? 25-year-old
James Nelson climbed into the back seat,
opened her purse, and took a black coin
purse containing her driver's license
and various debit, credit, and gift
cards. When Messerina asked what he was
doing, so she's conscious, just trapped
and with a hurt back. Nelson's
girlfriend, Mahogany Van, 24, allegedly
got in the p the front passenger seat
and began feeling around messena's
waistline as if searching for something.
Uh Nelson and Van fled as sirens
approached. Chicago firefighters
extricated Messarina from the wreckage
and took her to Mount Si where she soon
learned that two soon learned that two
of her debit cards were being used at a
gas station in the 500 block of South
California Avenue. According to
prosecutors
>> immediately started running it.
>> So you are driving along, you're a
normal contributing member of society.
You get hit and run by a black or an
illegal, right? Let's be honest. If I
was a betting man, black would be minus
300. Illegal would be minus 250. White
guy with insurance would be plus 9,000
or something. Yeah.
>> If I was a gambling man.
>> And uh everyone at least there's one
good Samaritan. Let him use the phone.
>> Held the phone up to your crumpled car
and body while it was flipped and said,
"Yeah, call 911." But you get hit and
run and then the the people steal from
you. So
>> yeah. And you can't say the word cuz
that would be a problem. You can't say a
certain sixletter word with a hard R at
the end of it because I don't know
>> that would be rude. That'd be violence.
>> You'd get fired or something. Yeah. And
the picture of the couple obviously. Uh
unckempt dreads. But you know if the
dreads, even if they aren't unckempt
from that man, the neck tattoo into the
dreads, that tells a whole different
story that supersedes any sort of
cleanliness of the dreads. I hope you
guys know that.
>> It's not a single variable thing.
>> Yeah. And like we always say, these
people weren't looking for, oh, we're
going to go do a crime today. They were
just walking by. They saw an
incapacitated person cuz they got into
an accident. And then they said, "Okay,
now we can do a quick crime."
>> Yep. Exactly. Opportunists.
>> And then let's go to the gas station and
buy whatever. Uh we have
>> What do you think they bought? Blunts
and
>> Blunts. Uh
>> some of that grape drink.
>> Yeah. Mad Dog 2020 if they got that.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And uh Yeah. Probably gas.
>> They're filling up other people's tanks
for 50 cents on a dollar
>> or for charity. give it back tidings.
>> Um, all right. Another person did a hit
and run and it killed somebody and
they're getting off pretty easy.
>> Lance's family and friends were in the
courtroom today. I actually just got a
text from Lance's partner and he tells
us that he's extremely disappointed in
the judge's verdict and his mother was
there as she tearfully described what
that loss has been over the last couple
of months. They also heard an a apology
from the woman who was responsible.
That's Kalandre Hood. She faced sin for
a felony hit and run an involuntarily
involuntary manslaughter. Lance Satello,
a Queen's University graduate and
runner, was hit in January at the Plaza
and 36th Street while out for a run.
Well, his mother told the judge she
forgives Hood, but she cannot forget.
Hood also stood and she apologized,
asking the family for forgiveness. She
said she wish she could turn back time.
I spoke with Lance's partner, as
mentioned, right before the sentencing
as well. He says, "Today was supposed to
be about accountability."
>> So, we're going to stop it there. You
understand it's a hit and run on a on a
jogger, a youngish man, and she got 30
days in jail and probation and then had
to pay $765 in restitution.
>> That's for the dead body.
>> That's for the dead guy who, you know,
probably could have lived if he had
gotten immediate medical attention. I
don't actually know the extent of the
injury.
>> Kill someone 700 bucks even.
>> But you certainly And then 30 days,
what? you miss your shitty job, you
know? It's not like you missed anything.
So,
>> you could like take a month off from
work and say, "Oh, I got some stuff
going on." And then like go back to work
and no one even knows.
>> Yeah. And uh there it's just kind of a
reminder. You know, we talked about
attempted murder being not enough of a
punishment. There's a lot of ways that
you can kill someone in America and get
kind of a light slap on the wrist. And
with your car is the is the best way to
do it. You can do a hit and run. You can
do whatever and it'll be involuntary
manslaughter. though.
>> Yeah, even when you ran on purpose.
>> Kind of a gap. Kind of a gap in uh like
I I I would trust that in
>> 1960 America probably, but given the way
people are swerving and driving and cell
phoning and musical.
>> Yeah.
>> All right, let's get to our next piece.
This is one I mentioned in the intro.
Um, a dad went to the bus stop because
his son was getting bullied and then the
bullies came off the bus to fight the
son in front of the dad and then the dad
pulled a gun to deescalate and then the
bullies are now the victims.
>> This is the video showing a 14-year-old
and 16year-old along with who we're told
is a parent to a student. Seconds in and
a gun is drawn.
>> I know it. I know it.
>> R.J. and Trevor are the two teens seen
in the video. R.J. tells me it started
with a fight between him and the man's
son.
>> So, I got off the bus, then we drop our
backpacks, we're about to fight. So,
then he tells the dad like, you know,
let him fight. Don't touch him. Don't do
none of that.
>> And then next thing you know, he put his
son behind him and he pulled a gun out
on us.
>> The 14 and 16year-olds say they put
their hands up and froze.
>> It's life or death right now. You know,
it's a gun. So, I'm backing up. I can't
process anything. I'm just like, am I
going to make it home? Martin County
Sheriff John Boonseek says no criminal
charges were filed in this case.
>> He's legally allowed to stand his
ground.
>> The sheriff says the whole incident
began when the man's son reported being
bullied the next day. The sheriff says
the father drove his son to the bus
stop.
>> The dad started talking again to the bus
driver, at which point the 14-year-old
took it upon himself to get off the bus
and confront the dead.
>> The sheriff tells us things only got
more heated from there. and they got all
the way up on him before he pulled out a
concealed weapon and told them to get
back, which he's legally allowed to do.
>> I feel like under any circumstance,
however you felt, no firearms should be
displayed at a bus stop where there's a
bunch of kids on the bus looking forward
to going to school.
>> The sheriff says the father is now
pulling his son out of school to
homeschool him. We're going to continue
following.
>> There you go. The kids getting
homeschooled, but uh a bunch of kids
looking forward to going to school. They
are just excited to get to class. And do
you guys know, it's so funny what you
tell the news versus what you see on
social media clips. Like, he got off the
bus to go do this and then pops off his
backpack and probably did one of these,
you know, those stupid black guy
fighting stances.
>> And then the other kid tells the dad,
"Don't get involved. Let us fight." And
then the dad just puts the kid behind
him, pulls out a gun, and was like, "No,
we're not doing that."
>> God bless the state of Florida and
sheriffs like that who come in and go,
"Yeah, nothing I can do." And I like how
every little single thing in the
newscast is kind of like a pulling at
your heartstrings. like this 14 and 16y
old. It's like, yeah, you can be a I saw
a bad 13-year-old who had like 30
felonies. Yeah.
>> You know, I I don't really care. Age
doesn't really matter. And also,
the funny part is I don't think anyone
should bring a gun to a to a school bus
stop. And it's like just what I'm
Everyone should be at the level that I
am, which is fighting with fists. Like
you you know, you don't get to dictate
terms when you're a criminal scumbag.
Yeah.
>> Threatening to beat people up. Like this
is exactly what guns are for.
>> Yeah,
>> it's a great equalizer. A few YN's come
up on you to jump your son. We weren't
going to jump him and stomp him out like
we show on the show twice a week for the
last four years.
>> I promise once you were knocked out I
wasn't going to kick your head three
extra times.
>> Yeah. Like this. Do we, you know, is
this what the guns are for or not?
>> Um but some of the funny lines, you
know, a bunch of kids looking forward to
going to school.
>> Is that what it was?
>> We told the dad to let us fight. And
then um some people were saying like,
"Oh, you should only use guns for
imminent danger." Why' they pull the gun
out? This is imminent danger. It's not
even close.
>> Stay your ground, brother. Stay on your
ground.
>> Decided to go to school. I don't know. Y
equals MX plus what?
>> Calculate the slope of this line. And
it's like a 45 degree angle. Easiest
line.
>> Yeah. 3 [snorts] * 3 * 3.
>> Yeah.
>> Um Yeah. So, that was pretty crazy. And
I'm glad that the sheriff didn't do
anything because you you got to be able
to This is what guns are for.
>> Yeah. That that's the perfect use. You
deescalated and settled and nobody got
hit.
>> Yeah.
>> And then everyone just got back on the
bus
>> and they probably aren't going to
with that kid anymore.
>> Well, he's home now.
>> And then here's a situation where a a
gun was inappropriately
uh drawn at a bus stop and no one really
heard of it.
>> Yeah, this is kind of going in our road
rage series, which we've randomly been
building up recently. Some of the worst
ones. Um you know, the getting honked at
is a big trigger, but we're going to
read the story. Armed woman allegedly
forced her way onto school bus during
Indianapolis road rage incident. Um, an
Indianapolis woman faces felony charges
after police say she forced her way onto
a school bus last week and waved a gun
during an apparent case of road rage.
Jia Sutton, 19, was arrested Wednesday
on the city's east side after
Indianapolis police were called to a
road rage incident involving a Kia K4
and a school bus with 37 children
inside.
>> Sure, she had a good reason. She
couldn't squash the beef. Ah, there kids
in there. Uh, she had to go do it.
>> The bus driver probably wasn't trying to
do anything to me personally.
>> IMPD officers were called on September
16th to the intersection of whatever in
reference to a vehicle accident. Upon
arrival, they found Sutton's Kia parked
sideways in front of the school bus and
blocking the roadway, like a GTA 6 move.
They soon determined that no vehicle
crash had occurred, but rather that
Sutton had hit a construction sign after
the school bus pulled out in front of
her. Sutton was reportedly angered and
thought the bus driver was at fault. So,
she told police she followed the bus. Uh
once she concluded that the bus was not
going to stop, Sutton told officers she
pulled her car around the bus and parked
crookedly on purpose in order to prevent
the bus from leaving. This is like
technically a light 38 counts of
kidnapping, [laughter] maybe, you know,
with the wrong DA. Uh, officers on scene
also spoke with a bus driver who said
that the bus never collided with
Sutton's car. The driver added that she
had never even noticed the Kia until it
pulled around in front of the bus and
stopped it from driving down the road.
The driver told officers that Sutton
then got out of her car armed with a
black handgun. Sutton then allegedly
began waving the handgun around, walking
around the bus, and yelling for the
driver to come outside. I'm sure it was,
you know, there's articles and then
there's what we show you on Urban Decay.
And I'm sure it was, "Come outside, Dan.
Come outside, Dan. Come outside then."
>> On our phone, too, like, "Come outside.
Come outside." When the driver refused
to leave the bus. Smart driver. You
don't really give in to the kidnapper
hostage situation. Uh, Sutton reportedly
forced the door open and came onto the
bus with the handgun. The 19-year-old
then waved the gun around and yelled at
the driver before leaving the bus and
returning to her parked car. So, cooler
heads, I guess, did prevail only after
you committed a felony. So, if you
weren't going to go all the way, I don't
know why you added the felony.
>> Crazy.
>> Uh, here's another little detail that I
found funny cuz it's like when they kind
of reference Urban Decay in an article.
It's always fascinating to me. You got
to read between the lines to do the peak
appropriate racism.
>> Uh, officers on scene asked Sutton
whether or not she threatened the driver
with a handgun, and she reportedly
admitted that she was armed during the
incident. However, she claimed she did
not do anything with it. When one IMPD
officer went to Sutton's car to turn
down the loud music she was playing,
they reportedly found a black handgun
under the driver's seat. So, the cops
come to the scene. She's already she's
stashed the gun, but her music is still
blasting in the clapped out Kia and uh
she just, you know, endanger the lives
of 37 kids. So,
>> I don't think it's good to be bringing a
gun to a bus stop. Like,
>> yeah, there you go. That's who did it.
Yep.
>> All right. Well, don't get too down or
too depressed. That's the end of Urban
Decay, but we're moving on to uplifting
gold, and we have uplifting stuff today.
>> Okay.
>> Uh, we have a couple fish related
things. This episode went long because
we were obviously off for a week, so
whatever. It's probably going to be two
hours.
>> Whatever.
>> Sorry to the editor, Nick.
>> And if you want more, there's bonus
land.
>> Yeah, but we just gave you a super long
episode. You want more?
>> Well, 30 minutes after that, bonus land
tomorrow. You know what to do. Go hit
the join button. All right. First, uh,
this guy's doing a joke about releasing
this fish near a shark.
>> Yeah, it's a shark.
>> You see how mad the shark is? So, he's
like going to release this thing and the
shark's just going in circles mad.
Thought that was so funny.
>> Okay.
>> Um, next, uh, this was in Cape Cod. Uh,
great white shark right on the beach.
>> Blood pile.
listening to Atlantis Moriceet.
Look at that. That's a great white right
there.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Isn't that crazy?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Um All right. Next, this cat catches a
fish.
Stray cat on a remote island.
He hears the sound. You see him
reacting. He's a hunter.
And the guy kind of like sets the scene
here. It's pretty cool.
Have the sunset with the cat
and then he gets it. And then the stray
That's what the stray cat eats. He eats
fish. That's cool, right? Isn't that
cool?
>> Yeah.
>> Stray cat catches fish.
>> Little tiger. They revert to being a
little tiger.
>> Yep. And this guy is Laian or Le
Oceanian.
>> Le Oceanian. Yeah. and uh he was living
in Louisiana and he got deported back to
Laos. So now he is a Louisiana accent
English speaker in Laos.
>> Yeah, I'm out here in Los man. I I don't
I don't know what village I'm at. I'm
out here. I got I got my buddy Kag with
me. Yeah, we out here on my uh on the
scooter loud style.
>> Y'all see that? Yeah. And look, this the
thing y'all see in LA sometime, bro.
When y'all ride, look got a whole albino
ax, man. Yeah.
>> Water buffalo.
>> Water buffalo. Yeah,
>> that's pretty cool. He seems like a nice
guy, but you still have to go back.
>> Yeah, that's fine. You know, you can be
nice anywhere. Like I That's what I'm
saying. I would be so respectful to
Indian people if they just stayed in
India.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, that's it.
>> So true. Um and also like if he's in
Laos now teaching people English,
there's going to be like maybe a
>> Yeah. a pocket of like people in Laos
that speak English with the Louisiana
accent which like
>> similar to the Red Sox playing the Cubs
at Tropicana Field.
>> It's a glitch.
>> It's a glitch in the Matrix.
>> Yeah.
>> And our Pure Americana clip of the week,
our last piece of the show is the
Minnesota [music] State Fair goat
contest. Is that what it is?
>> These llamas.
>> Llamas.
>> Yeah, they look like llamas.
>> And we'll just kind of show a bunch in
the background and go through some of
these videos. But what do they do?
>> They dress up the llamas.
>> School bus llama. We got Woody, Toy
Story llama.
>> Yeah.
>> Thing one, Thing Two, llama.
>> So, there's like a llama contest in
Minnesota and there's no Somali.
>> Oh, wait a second.
>> Wait a sec.
>> Who's this Indian guy or Somali?
>> Saw him.
>> Couldn't be there.
>> They don't appreciate this. They don't
get why we do this. They go, "Oh, you
you don't have sex with the llama.
>> You you dress him up instead." That was
a low hanging fruit.
>> Yeah, it's pretty lowbrow. But you know
what? Honestly, speaking of lowbrow
pure racist stuff or whatever you
want to say, we're entitled to a little.
>> Yeah. After what they did to us, I'm
entitled to a little lowbrow, loweffort
racism. Me, too. All right. We have a a
couple small business shoutouts. We're
going to keep going and doing these all
through October. So, if you haven't
heard yours called yet, it's coming. I
have them all in order, and we're
working our way through the list.
Remember to give these companies
fivestar reviews if you've used their
services and if you need their services,
you hit them up. These are all showing
companies and they're good small
business ownering people.
>> Cool.
>> First is Paul Paloski. P A W L O S KI.
Polish, right? Yeah.
>> Paloski. Well, and Pump.
>> It's probably Pavloki
>> cuz sometimes they do the W for the V
and Pavlo. So, it's everything's linked
in the description. So links for all
these are going to be at the bottom of
the description uh for the YouTube
video. Um but it's pavloski
wellandpump.com.
This is in the Grand Rapids, Michigan
area. They do well inspections, well
cleanings, chlorination, water sampling,
pump and pressure tank replacement, and
complete well replacements. So check
them out if you guys need some well
work. And we have a picture.
>> It's a nice rig.
>> We have a picture of them with the rig.
>> That's a nice [music] rig.
>> That's pretty cool.
>> I like a Polish guy in Michigan. Me too.
>> Stand tall, brother.
>> So, give them a good review if you've
used their services or use their
services. Um, Cosmic Mermaid. This is a
a children's book and it's on Amazon.
Link in the description. It's a great
read for boys and girls under seven. The
author is a showwatcher. Um, and it's a
great gift for Christmas or a baby
shower. It's called Cosmic Mermaid. It's
a show watcher authored book by a lovely
woman who watches the show. And go get
it. Great. Very cool. And then we also
have ftgaccounting.com.
So this is a virtual accounting service
for individuals or small business
owners. They do tax prep, monthly uh
book monthly bookkeeping, financial
analysis, and consulting in general.
These guys are great. ftgacounting.com,
they're linked. Uh they're super good
show watchers, and the guy is a great
guy.
>> Awesome. And then [music] our last small
business shout out is Garbaggen Knight.
Knobbaggen
knight LLC.com. They take your cans to
their garbage cans to the curb and back
as their business and it's very
affordable and it's in Monmouth and
Ocean County, New Jersey right now and
they're expanding. But it's great for
people who are property managers, HOAs,
Airbnbs, elderly, or just people who are
busy in general.
>> Yeah.
>> And uh they'll take your cans to the
curb and back uh for a very affordable
price. I think they have 2 weeks free.
Try for 14 days for free. And they made
a video. This is who we're supporting.
>> Because words are just words until trash
day actually starts. But actions speak
louder than words. And words speak
louder than actions. But sometimes
garbage night can take your hands to the
curb
>> because sometimes listening to a flex
talk podcast is the right thing to do.
>> Very good. [laughter]
>> Garbage night.
>> Isn't that cool?
>> Eventually the garbage night they they
upsell you on the cleaning.
>> Yeah.
>> Clean the can, too. It's good business.
>> Of course. Once your can goes bad, it
goes bad.
>> Yeah. This is what white guys are up to
now. They have to invent businesses, you
know.
>> We got to support them.
>> We got to support them. if you're in New
Jersey in those two towns or Ocean
County or give them a great review if
you use their services. They're great.
>> That's the key.
>> That's the key. All right, we have some
happy birthdays. We have happy birthday
to Tyler on September 26. Him and Pita
[music] love the show. We know Pita.
>> We've heard this name before.
>> We know Pita. Our our Latina type names
stand out. [music]
>> Yes, very much.
>> So, wait, so whose birthday was it?
>> Tyler's.
>> Happy birthday, Tyler. And and good day
to you, Pita.
>> Hello, Perita. Um, and they spread the
show to everyone they know, [music]
which is important. Good. And then we
have a happy birthday to Chandler who
turned 30 on September 21st, [music] and
he lives in Hawaii. So, him and Lyanna
and their dog Chuck love the show. I
didn't know people lived in Hawaii.
>> It's hard to do.
>> Expensive, you know? They hate white
people and
>> Yeah, he could be there for some sort of
military reason. Maybe maybe he's in the
hospitality industry.
>> There's there's reasons to be in Hawaii.
I was joking about I didn't know people
could live in Hawaii. Um, happy birthday
[music] to Rich on September 22nd. Rich
spent the last year and a half
dedicating himself to God and his health
and his family [music] and everyone is
loving it. So, good stuff, Rich. Keep up
the good work. We love you, too.
>> There you go. Very nice. Happy birthday
[music] to Sedona. She turned seven last
week and she's been watching the show
since before episode 100. We have a
picture of her watching here with her
brother. We love you guys. God bless.
Thank you for watching and happy
birthday.
>> Happy birthday, [music] Sedona. Look at
you're on the show now.
>> You're on the show. You're right there.
>> I don't know, man. How comfortable am I
with this type of children watching the
show?
>> I think they understand. Okay.
>> They understand the understandable
concepts. [music]
>> Parental discretion. I guess
>> parental discretion is advised.
>> Hey, it's your kid.
>> It's your child.
>> Yeah, parental discretion is advised.
>> Yeah, we should say something. [music]
>> But advised just means you decide.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Happy birthday to Christina who turned
one year older on September 25th.
>> Okay. Hey. Uh she's an amazing mom to
her two uh to her two girls. She has uh
two daughters with her and Josh are a
nice couple and uh they're also bonus
landers and they watch every episode
[music] together. So happy birthday,
Christina. Sorry I kind of botched it.
>> Sounds good. Happy birthday, Christina.
You sound like my grandma who was 39 for
her whole life.
>> There you go.
>> Yeah. One year older. I'm not telling
you my age.
>> Well, I think she just didn't include
it.
>> Okay.
>> And then I just kind of assumed
>> she went up a year.
>> Yes. And then we have a shout out to
Dena the Beina and Mace. [music]
Congrats on your seventh wedding
anniversary. We we're really glad you
guys love the show. Keep going strong.
[music]
Seven more years of marriage minimum.
>> Yeah. I don't think you're supposed to
[music] say that, you know. Best wishes
to everything.
>> 10 more years of marriage. I don't know
how how much you want.
>> How long are we all really going to
>> How much you guys want to do?
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Till death do his part, I guess.
>> Death. [music] Yes. Yes. Exactly. So
hopefully you guys are married forever.
All right. All right. Well, that's the
end of the show. Thank you guys for
watching all the way through on this
extra long episode. But you know what? I
kind of like a 2-hour episode. Those are
rare.
>> We owe you guy. You know, we owe you.
And if you want even more, there was so
many things we couldn't cover. There's
like this trans [music] crazy killer
that we're going to cover in bonus land.
Really good bon probably one of our best
bonus lands [music] coming tomorrow. So,
please hit that join button. You'll see
it right here on YouTube. The playlist
gets updated. I post it to the group
chat. Thank you guys for [music]
watching all the way through. Like,
share, subscribe, all the good stuff. We
will see you at bonus land tomorrow.
[music]
When you feel like the world is
backwards and upside down.
Notifications [music]
on and then you hear the sound.
We're heading to the bathroom. You know
we got to go
cuz flick is [music] a rap just
the show
is [music]
fl
[music]
the only way to
>> [music]
>> can be defined.
The best news [music]
of all time
[music]
on the last page of housekeeping. We're
letting flags cook.
There's a new alien [music] spin. Red
boy shoes my love.
It's exactly what the f [music]
wouldn't want you to see.
But it [music] could be a distraction
and that rings true to me.
[music]
his tongs. Flickle
the post.
The only way to shine [music]
can't be defined.
The best news podcast [music]
of all time.
We're yapping [music] in the comments.
Yapping in the comments. [music]
Don't get too down [music]
or too depressed from cringe of the week
and urban decay. This uplifting [music]
gold and fleck his pets get controlled
coming up to biting your day. [music]
The only way the sh
can [music] be divine.
The best news
of [music] all time
to keep the PO box full.
We won't [music] stop till the world is
rid of all the pit bulls.
[music]
If more flex content is what you demand,
then just [music] make sure you're sub
to bonus land.
Fl's [music]
best host.
Flu [music]
go and tick all the post.
The only way to shine
can be defined.
The best news
of all time. [music]
We're watching old episodes.
Yeah. Watching old episodes.
[music]
We're still kicking [music] over stacked
rocks.
The only way to show [music]
can be defined.
The best [music] news
of all times [music]
like action
with me as I do my makeup before [music]
my game in front of thousands of people
as a professional baseball player.
>> [laughter]